<library>
    <categories>
        <category>
            <id>e425fa677bdeec8d601df63539f5e217</id>
            <name>Humor</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>9b4bdac9d49a1bb15baca377b3555ee6</id>
            <name>Christian</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>751e1e294ec372b2b742fee4a8c5b4ed</id>
            <name>Short Stories</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</id>
            <name>Fantasy</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>b942462de516c69a778d56ccae99fd15</id>
            <name>Biography</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>20092b926d220487bd8e9915f57dfbb2</id>
            <name>Historical</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>047fd63c5e8739f61e1540dc8896e249</id>
            <name>Adult Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>0caea5b38e9afeceae2c30e217670826</id>
            <name>Christian Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>29e4a3e5b5a3c7fa2cdb4779729a375c</id>
            <name>Food and Drink</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>d1100b5cbc1d9411d3dfd60e6538aa61</id>
            <name>Sports and Games</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>974e4096879babaabd1fea89161d57a1</id>
            <name>Politics</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>85ffc60d416c2608725907a85fa969db</id>
            <name>Science</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>0f4974973a2a0372613bd44f7f288a17</id>
            <name>Self Help</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>5f3f6372f39c152e3848fd216044b357</id>
            <name>Womens Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>918fb36d8a46947e3198f2008d2d1c52</id>
            <name>Autobiography</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>761c2eba5204d2f04efdd2322f6e3e7c</id>
            <name>Paranormal</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</id>
            <name>Sequential Art</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>383351f1704abf38d77ea6ea4bac1fd5</id>
            <name>Business</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>e1f247894e1b3443c16bd40b30dde694</id>
            <name>Health</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>b7ef718d31a4168926dfa17154e617b3</id>
            <name>Parenting</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>4d561fe7c23a5e1af24db58ab931f61f</id>
            <name>Spirituality</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>34c17060c25f5164cb42f091b8c5b044</id>
            <name>Suspense</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>316b4899867ffb0d5a3cd904a1c75867</id>
            <name>Young Adult</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>75a33864a7bed7bb1016d61ec8db5db6</id>
            <name>Novels</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>bb7dd6d6ce48535fde2cd59b3e02c9f9</id>
            <name>Philosophy</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>2cd19deab9ef0b88bd2181888ebb9bd0</id>
            <name>Thriller</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>b6fd3641fbebc17c4f90c5e6ce396069</id>
            <name>New Adult</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>3aae92034c4be904847d47db512438b3</id>
            <name>Historical Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</id>
            <name>Nonfiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>1d4d39d152711c55a32fa4724cec47e2</id>
            <name>Travel</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>a9a8dcfa66cfe6d431ed158c72efd11f</id>
            <name>Music</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>4135e65298f9865968b7b28f0f69e490</id>
            <name>Religion</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>6112a5d6a2426a5f910395b55f1b3800</id>
            <name>Erotica</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>115c4bb892c6e92e7300d57d705e7314</id>
            <name>History</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>43065d6ba008562c23134dc998b3e6ac</id>
            <name>Science Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>280a530c4c5e7c6d9f5e2ef32cdf82d6</id>
            <name>Mystery</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>7f40b6a41770642af928f12b6843e4fe</id>
            <name>Crime</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</id>
            <name>Romance</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>ba67033c9741930192689a2e7e007b29</id>
            <name>Poetry</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>94579d5666d9575b6b2e6130d00c60b5</id>
            <name>Psychology</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>8f67479d76bd33a8c33519a169c2184d</id>
            <name>Classics</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</id>
            <name>Childrens</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>6161564899ac6d10decca00d60477454</id>
            <name>Art</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>7cf47a36ee3fc786b75a977365348b19</id>
            <name>Cultural</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</id>
            <name>Fiction</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>1cf5299dd4b5deb500079f922c5c591b</id>
            <name>Horror</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>f2c97a69f3ec3378fa4429433c6b270b</id>
            <name>Academic</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</id>
            <name>Default</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</id>
            <name>Add a comment</name>
        </category>
        <category>
            <id>863e7da66ddf3e0ce21d2a543d1395d4</id>
            <name>Contemporary</name>
        </category>
    </categories>
    <books>
        <book>
            <id>acd2b8aaa135caa0a99276df1ea052d2</id>
            <title>Carry On, Warrior: Thoughts on Life Unarmed</title>
            <price>31.85</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>An inspirational, sidesplittingly funny exploration of the power of living with love,
                forgiveness, and honesty.In Carry On, Warrior, Glennon Doyle Melton shares new stories and the
                best-loved material from Momastery.com She recounts her mistakes and triumphs with candor and humor, and
                gives language to our universal (yet often secret) experiences. She believes that by shed An
                inspirational, sidesplittingly funny exploration of the power of living with love, forgiveness, and
                honesty.In Carry On, Warrior, Glennon Doyle Melton shares new stories and the best-loved material from
                Momastery.com She recounts her mistakes and triumphs with candor and humor, and gives language to our
                universal (yet often secret) experiences. She believes that by shedding our armor, we can stop hiding,
                competing, striving for the mirage of perfection, and making motherhood, marriage, and friendship harder
                by pretending they’re not hard. In this one woman trying to love herself and others, readers find a wise
                and witty friend who will inspire them to forgive their own imperfections, make the most of their gifts,
                and commit to small acts of love that will change the world. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/dd/f5/ddf5da673bb34a74a81faf7271c7ca13.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>19ea2e59fe8ca7b9898ea669595c3a8b</id>
            <title>The Paris Wife</title>
            <price>36.8</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>A deeply evocative story of ambition and betrayal, The Paris Wife captures a remarkable period
                of time and a love affair between two unforgettable people: Ernest Hemingway and his wife
                Hadley.Chicago, 1920: Hadley Richardson is a quiet twenty-eight-year-old who has all but given up on
                love and happiness—until she meets Ernest Hemingway and her life changes forever. Followi A deeply
                evocative story of ambition and betrayal, The Paris Wife captures a remarkable period of time and a love
                affair between two unforgettable people: Ernest Hemingway and his wife Hadley.Chicago, 1920: Hadley
                Richardson is a quiet twenty-eight-year-old who has all but given up on love and happiness—until she
                meets Ernest Hemingway and her life changes forever. Following a whirlwind courtship and wedding, the
                pair set sail for Paris, where they become the golden couple in a lively and volatile group—the fabled
                “Lost Generation”—that includes Gertrude Stein, Ezra Pound, and F. Scott and Zelda Fitzgerald. Though
                deeply in love, the Hemingways are ill-prepared for the hard-drinking and fast-living life of Jazz Age
                Paris, which hardly values traditional notions of family and monogamy. Surrounded by beautiful women and
                competing egos, Ernest struggles to find the voice that will earn him a place in history, pouring all
                the richness and intensity of his life with Hadley and their circle of friends into the novel that will
                become The Sun Also Rises. Hadley, meanwhile, strives to hold on to her sense of self as the demands of
                life with Ernest grow costly and her roles as wife, friend, and muse become more challenging. Despite
                their extraordinary bond, they eventually find themselves facing the ultimate crisis of their marriage—a
                deception that will lead to the unraveling of everything they’ve fought so hard for. A heartbreaking
                portrayal of love and torn loyalty, The Paris Wife is all the more poignant because we know that, in the
                end, Hemingway wrote that he would rather have died than fallen in love with anyone but Hadley. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/01/c8/01c847671683538fcf084eede54d6270.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>6ad10cebea190c93697a5d17bf8de1e0</id>
            <title>Amy Meets the Saints and Sages</title>
            <price>18.46</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>All major religions have saints and sages that are pinnacles of love and integrity. Wouldn't
                your child benefit from having them as role models? Wouldn't it empower your child to know that these
                saints/sages are real people, some of whom are living right now?In "Amy Meets the Saints and Sages, A
                Young Person's Adventures in Spirituality" your child gets to meet six saints/ All major religions have
                saints and sages that are pinnacles of love and integrity. Wouldn't your child benefit from having them
                as role models? Wouldn't it empower your child to know that these saints/sages are real people, some of
                whom are living right now?In "Amy Meets the Saints and Sages, A Young Person's Adventures in
                Spirituality" your child gets to meet six saints/sages from six different traditions: Islam,
                Catholicism, Judaism, Native American, Tibetan Buddhism, and Hinduism. Three of the saints/sages are
                women; three are men. Three are still with us; three have passed on. Your child is introduced to these
                saints/sages first through a brief but reverent biography. Then second, your child gets to know the
                saint/sage better through a concrete story. Children love stories and they have a way of sticking to a
                child for years. And finally, let's make it personal by having the saint/sage and a young person, about
                your child's age, fictionally interact around the story. It's all fun and engaging for both child and
                adults.It's for children age 7-12 and is fully illustrated. There is never any attempt to have your
                child join anything.And, as your child comes to appreciate various religions, a bit more religious
                tolerance is gained. With that gain a bit more peace has come forth.Find out more at
                http://www.mychildsprayers.com/amy-me... ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/00/53/0053efa8515b8e2ad9b029c298766e9f.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>b62f36ea3d97882562ed96be4191ea43</id>
            <title>The Perfect Play (Play by Play #1)</title>
            <price>59.99</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Football pro Mick Riley is an all-star, both on the field and in the bedroom. But a sexy,
                determinedly single mom just might be the one to throw him off his game...For years Mick has been taking
                full advantage of the life available to a pro athlete: fame, fortune, and a different girl in every
                city. But when he meets and beds confident, beautiful event planner Tara Lincoln Football pro Mick Riley
                is an all-star, both on the field and in the bedroom. But a sexy, determinedly single mom just might be
                the one to throw him off his game...For years Mick has been taking full advantage of the life available
                to a pro athlete: fame, fortune, and a different girl in every city. But when he meets and beds
                confident, beautiful event planner Tara Lincoln, he wants much more than the typical one-night stand.
                Too bad Tara's not interested in getting to know football's most notorious playboy any better.As the
                single mother of a teenage son, the last thing Tara needs is the jet-set lifestyle of Mick Riley; even
                though their steamy and passionate one-night stand was unforgettable. Tara's life is complicated enough
                without being thrust into the spotlight as Mick's latest girl du jour. Tara played the game of love once
                and lost big, and she doesn't intend to put herself out there again, especially with a heartbreaker like
                Mick.But when Mick sets his mind to win, nothing will stop him. And he has the perfect play in mind.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/40/16/4016ffba678f309171d8130135f6eb8e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e108aa1e08b4408335cc261154b26d39</id>
            <title>The First Hostage (J.B. Collins #2)</title>
            <price>25.85</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>“The president of the United States . . . is missing.”With these words, New York Times
                journalist J. B. Collins, reporting from the scene of a devastating attack by ISIS terrorists in Amman,
                Jordan, puts the entire world on high alert. The leaders of Israel and Palestine are critically injured,
                Jordan’s king is fighting for his life, and the U.S. president is missing and p “The president of the
                United States . . . is missing.”With these words, New York Times journalist J. B. Collins, reporting
                from the scene of a devastating attack by ISIS terrorists in Amman, Jordan, puts the entire world on
                high alert. The leaders of Israel and Palestine are critically injured, Jordan’s king is fighting for
                his life, and the U.S. president is missing and presumed captured.As the U.S. government faces a
                constitutional crisis and Jordan battles for its very existence, Collins must do his best to keep the
                world informed while working to convince the FBI that his stories are not responsible for the terror
                attack on the Jordanian capital. And ISIS still has chemical weapons . . .Struggling to clear his name,
                Collins and the Secret Service try frantically to locate and rescue the leader of the free world before
                ISIS’s threats become a catastrophic reality. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/38/34/3834572e651cdc14b18d348fa4875aa9.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>bd98c49a2939ae637ab801c26944b1a8</id>
            <title>The Silent Twin (Detective Jennifer Knight #3)</title>
            <price>36.25</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>I’m alone in the dark, please can you find me …Nine-year-old twins Abigail and Olivia vow never
                to be parted. But when Abigail goes missing from Blackwater Farm, DC Jennifer Knight must find her
                before it’s too late. Twin sister Olivia has been mute since Abigail’s disappearance. But when she
                whispers in Jennifer’s ear, Jennifer realises it is Abigail’s voice pleading to b I’m alone in the dark,
                please can you find me …Nine-year-old twins Abigail and Olivia vow never to be parted. But when Abigail
                goes missing from Blackwater Farm, DC Jennifer Knight must find her before it’s too late. Twin sister
                Olivia has been mute since Abigail’s disappearance. But when she whispers in Jennifer’s ear, Jennifer
                realises it is Abigail’s voice pleading to be found. A damp and decaying house set in acres of desolate
                scrubland, the farm is a place of secrets, old and new – and Jennifer must unravel them all in order to
                find the lost girl. But could Olivia’s bond with her twin hold the key to finding Abigail? And can
                Jennifer break through her silence in time to save her sister’s life? A darkly gripping, page-turning
                thriller that will enthrall fans of Rachel Abbott, Alex Marwood’s The Wicked Girls and Mark Edwards.
                Praise for Caroline Mitchell:‘Fan-bloody-tastic! I enjoyed this book so much that I forced myself to
                read slowly as I just could not bear for it to end… I thought the story was brilliant. The characters
                were creative and kept me hooked. ‘The twists and turns kept me gasping for more… Could not recommend
                this book any more highly!’ Crime Book Junkie ‘This is a well written supernatural detective story, with
                a surprising twist that I guarantee will keep you glued to the last page… at times I couldn’t turn the
                pages quickly enough, it’s atmospheric, gritty and at times just plain scary, and what a twist at the
                end.’ The Book Review Café ‘With a brilliant cast of crime characters, and a plot that was enough to
                make me feel dizzy, this was a compelling book that I just couldn't get enough of. Every word, every
                page, every murder, every guess... I couldn't wait for the final piece of the jigsaw to fit into place…
                the word 'thrilling' just doesn't do this justice.’ Becca’s Books ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a0/7b/a07b53e1708f9055145aa1ec3af8608d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f0844aed13f51403025bc6dd7a8aa904</id>
            <title>A Murder Over a Girl: Justice, Gender, Junior High</title>
            <price>13.2</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>A psychologist's gripping, troubling, and moving exploration of the brutal murder of a possibly
                transgender middle school student by an eighth grade classmateOn Feb. 12, 2008, at E. O. Green Junior
                High in Oxnard, CA, 14-year-old Brandon McInerney shot and killed his classmate, Larry King, who had
                recently begun to call himself "Leticia" and wear makeup and jewelry to scho A psychologist's gripping,
                troubling, and moving exploration of the brutal murder of a possibly transgender middle school student
                by an eighth grade classmateOn Feb. 12, 2008, at E. O. Green Junior High in Oxnard, CA, 14-year-old
                Brandon McInerney shot and killed his classmate, Larry King, who had recently begun to call himself
                "Leticia" and wear makeup and jewelry to school.Profoundly shaken by the news, and unsettled by media
                coverage that sidestepped the issues of gender identity and of race integral to the case, psychologist
                Ken Corbett traveled to LA to attend the trial. As visions of victim and perpetrator were woven and
                unwoven in the theater of the courtroom, a haunting picture emerged not only of the two young teenagers,
                but also of spectators altered by an atrocity and of a community that had unwittingly gestated a murder.
                Drawing on firsthand observations, extensive interviews and research, as well as on his decades of
                academic work on gender and sexuality, Corbett holds each murky facet of this case up to the light,
                exploring the fault lines of memory and the lacunae of uncertainty behind facts. Deeply compassionate,
                and brimming with wit and acute insight, A Murder Over a Girl is a riveting and stranger-than-fiction
                drama of the human psyche. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/56/31/56313728d302c83f2a8c70fba635ce33.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>33603dc440619d61848e27dba33b9e56</id>
            <title>The Art of Startup Fundraising</title>
            <price>21</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>The Art of Startup Fundraising takes a fresh look at raising money for startups, with a focus
                on the changing face of startup finance. New regulations are making the old go-to advice less relevant,
                as startup money is increasingly moving online. These new waters are all but uncharted—and founders need
                an accessible guide. This book helps you navigate the online world of st The Art of Startup Fundraising
                takes a fresh look at raising money for startups, with a focus on the changing face of startup finance.
                New regulations are making the old go-to advice less relevant, as startup money is increasingly moving
                online. These new waters are all but uncharted—and founders need an accessible guide. This book helps
                you navigate the online world of startup fundraising with easy-to-follow explanations and expert
                perspective on the new digital world of finance. You'll find tips and tricks on raising money and
                investing in startups from early stage to growth stage, and develop a clear strategy based on the new
                realities surrounding today's startup landscape.The finance world is in a massive state of flux. Changes
                are occurring at an increasing pace in all sectors, but few more intensely than the startup sphere. When
                the paradigm changes, your processes must change with it. This book shows you how startup funding works,
                with expert coaching toward the new rules on the field.-Learn how the JOBS Act impacts the fundraising
                model-Gain insight on startups from early stage to growth stage-Find the money you need to get your
                venture going-Craft your pitch and optimize the strategy-Build momentum-Identify the right
                investors-Avoid the common mistakesDon't rely on the "how we did it" tales from superstar startups, as
                these stories are unique and applied to exceptional scenarios. The game has changed, and playing by the
                old rules only gets you left behind. Whether you're founding a startup or looking to invest, The Art of
                Startup Fundraising provides the up-to-the-minute guidance you need.PRAISE FOR THE ART OF STARTUP
                FUNDRAISING:“The Art of Startup Fundraising is a must read for anyone who even considers starting a
                business. Fundraising is hard. This book gives you the roadmap to get where you are going. Alejandro
                Cremades speaks with wisdom and from experience.“ - Tim Draper , Founder of Draper Associates, DFJ, and
                Draper University."The Art of Startup Fundraising should be a mandatory reading for entrepreneurs that
                are looking to raise capital. This book will enable Alejandro to help many more early stage companies
                answer the tough questions when fundraising." - Marco Landi, Former Chief Operating Officer at Apple and
                Chairman at Atlantis Ventures"Raising capital is often the most daunting and least understood aspects of
                starting a new business and there are few people more experienced than Alejandro Cremades to act as a
                guide. The Art of Startup Fundraising unlocks key secrets of fundraising for newly minted
                entrepreneurs." - Jeff Stibel, Chairman of BrainGate, Inc. and Vice Chairman of Dun &amp; Bradstreet,
                Inc.; New York Times bestselling author of Breakpoint and Wired for Thought."This book provides a clear,
                concise tour of the fundraising game. With his crowdfunding and entrepreneurial expertise in full
                display, Cremades does a terrific job making a complicated process simple and accessible." - Jeff
                Bussgang, General Partner at Flybridge Capital Partners and Senior Lecturer at Harvard Business
                School“Entrepreneurs need to be amazing at recruiting, selling and fundraising. The Art of Startup
                Fundraising provides the essential toolkit for mastering a core skill for any entrepreneur.” - Gil
                Penchina, serial entrepreneur and prolific angel investor“For many entrepreneurs finding the right
                investor for their venture can be a daunting task. Alejandro's experience with equity crowdfunding gives
                a unique perspective on the fundraising game. The Art of Startup Fundraising is very insightful for
                entrepreneurs looking to close a round of financing and changing the world.” - Anyndya Ghose, Professor
                at NYU Stern School of Business“There is no perfect approach to raising investment for a startup, but
                there is a certain tribal knowledge out there, that most of us had to learn through several failed
                attempts. The Art of Startup Fundraising captures every bit of advice (and then some!) that I would give
                to any entrepreneur looking for funding.” - Paul Murphy, Partner at Betaworks and CoFounder of
                Playdots“Alejandro's The Art of Startup Fundraising is a must read for any entrepreneur. Clear and
                concise, he outlines in today's startup community the steps to successfully fundraise. This is the
                golden era for entrepreneurs, any good idea with proof of concept can get access to money. Know your
                options!” - Angelo J. Robles, Founder and CEO of Family Office Association“It doesn't matter how great
                of a business you can build. If you can't raise money, you're toast. Master this book.” - Ilya Pozin,
                Forbes Contributor and CoFounder of Pluto TV and CoFounder of Coplex"The Art of Startup Fundraising
                translates art into science. By sharing proven formulas, strategies, and case studies that work,
                Alejandro Cremades provides a needed service to future entrepreneurs." - Josh Cohen, Managing Partner at
                City Light Capital“This ought to be a reading requirement for all entrepreneurs when building a business
                and raising capital. This is a very well written and informative book, written by a man who is a
                testament to dedication and creativity when confronted with the challenges of being an entrepreneur and
                raising capital.” - Carter Caldwell, serial entrepreneur and Principal at Cross Atlantic Capital
                Partners“Alejandro is on the bleeding edge of equity crowdfunding today. When he talks about
                fundraising, startups listen.” - Andrew Ackerman, Managing Director at Dreamit Ventures“Raising capital
                can be tough. Alejandro provides a step-by-step guidebook to all entrepreneurs that rather spend their
                time thinking about changing the world instead of thinking of how to raise funds.” - Tobias P. Schirmer,
                Managing Partner of JOIN Capital "A superb book on fundraising. Alejandro's guidance should arm
                entrepreneurs with the necessary tools to close with success a meaningful round of financing." - Ellen
                Weber, Executive Director at Robin Hood Ventures“The Art of Startup Fundraising is a practical and
                comprehensive resource for entrepreneurs to use again and again. It captures what startups need to do to
                be successful in the rapidly evolving financing world, while also providing tips on the fundamentals of
                building businesses that don’t change over time.” - Marianne Hudson, Executive Director at Angel Capital
                Association“Raising money is hard. But start-up founders all over the world can make it exponentially
                easier by educating themselves on the process of raising equity capital before they dive into it. The
                practical, hands-on advice from Alejandro Cremades in this book provides a solid foundation in that
                self-education process. Delivered in an approachable format with a key lesson to take-away every few
                pages, “The Art of Startup Fundraising” is essential reading for entrepreneurs everywhere.” - Allen
                Taylor, Managing Director at Endeavor ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>383351f1704abf38d77ea6ea4bac1fd5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/b3/7b/b37be83183f1dcb759d92bda8f8998a4.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d6b9b6d596599c7582951650b5df9d96</id>
            <title>A Clash of Kings (A Song of Ice and Fire #2)</title>
            <price>10.79</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>Alternate cover edition can be found here. Time is out of joint. The summer of peace and
                plenty, ten years long, is drawing to a close, and the harsh, chill winter approaches like an angry
                beast. Two great leaders—Lord Eddard Stark and Robert Baratheon—who held sway over an age of enforced
                peace are dead...victims of royal treachery. Now, from the ancient citadel of Dragon Alternate cover
                edition can be found here. Time is out of joint. The summer of peace and plenty, ten years long, is
                drawing to a close, and the harsh, chill winter approaches like an angry beast. Two great leaders—Lord
                Eddard Stark and Robert Baratheon—who held sway over an age of enforced peace are dead...victims of
                royal treachery. Now, from the ancient citadel of Dragonstone to the forbidding shores of Winterfell,
                chaos reigns, as pretenders to the Iron Throne of the Seven Kingdoms prepare to stake their claims
                through tempest, turmoil, and war. As a prophecy of doom cuts across the sky—a comet the color of blood
                and flame—six factions struggle for control of a divided land. Eddard's son Robb has declared himself
                King in the North. In the south, Joffrey, the heir apparent, rules in name only, victim of the scheming
                courtiers who teem over King's Landing. Robert's two brothers each seek their own dominion, while a
                disfavored house turns once more to conquest. And a continent away, an exiled queen, the Mother of
                Dragons, risks everything to lead her precious brood across a hard hot desert to win back the crown that
                is rightfully hers. A Clash of Kings transports us into a magnificent, forgotten land of revelry and
                revenge, wizardry and wartime. It is a tale in which maidens cavort with madmen, brother plots against
                brother, and the dead rise to walk in the night. Here a princess masquerades as an orphan boy; a knight
                of the mind prepares a poison for a treacherous sorceress; and wild men descend from the Mountains of
                the Moon to ravage the countryside. Against a backdrop of incest and fratricide, alchemy and murder, the
                price of glory may be measured in blood. And the spoils of victory may just go to the men and women
                possessed of the coldest steel...and the coldest hearts. For when rulers clash, all of the land feels
                the tremors. Audacious, inventive, brilliantly imagined, A Clash of Kings is a novel of dazzling beauty
                and boundless enchantment;a tale of pure excitement you will never forget. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/1a/29/1a298a157f4113d6e0127521aaa1f5f0.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9050ee402c9e7e3567bc380e5cdfd798</id>
            <title>Off the Hook (Fishing for Trouble #1)</title>
            <price>47.67</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>Welcome to The Buoys, a West Coast haven where love comes in with the tide. Perfect for readers
                of Jill Shalvis and Susan Mallery, the Fishing for Trouble series features three unforgettable
                brothers—each of whom is a great catch.Major league pitcher Liam O'Donnell knows his best days are
                probably behind him, but that doesn't mean he's ready to retire and become a fishing Welcome to The
                Buoys, a West Coast haven where love comes in with the tide. Perfect for readers of Jill Shalvis and
                Susan Mallery, the Fishing for Trouble series features three unforgettable brothers—each of whom is a
                great catch.Major league pitcher Liam O'Donnell knows his best days are probably behind him, but that
                doesn't mean he's ready to retire and become a fishing guide. Still, after all the time he's spent
                chasing his dreams, he owes it to his brothers to pull his weight around the lodge. The Buoys is their
                father's legacy, and they can't let some developer take it from them. The one snag Liam isn't counting
                on is a blast from the past: his ex-wife.The moment Kate Hadley steps out of the seaplane, she knows
                this assignment is going to be trickier than she thought. She has to persuade the owners to sell—and one
                of them is Liam O'Donnell. Ten years ago, she made the biggest mistake of her life when she married Liam
                during a fling in Vegas. Now he's her only lifeline in the middle of nowhere. Kate's trying to keep
                things cool, but Liam just reminds her of the scorching few nights they spent together—and tempts her to
                make new memories that are just as steamy as the old. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/1d/78/1d78fe226e1adb9cb591fa21f8a9bf68.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d192aa28ddf244b5a1d5a5e893b66fbc</id>
            <title>Feathers: Displays of Brilliant Plumage</title>
            <price>49.05</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>Exquisite images from award-winning National Geographic photographer Robert Clark offer a
                captivating perspective on the vast beauty and myriad functions of a seemingly simple thing: the bird
                feather. Each detailed close-up is paired with informative text about the utility and evolution of the
                feather it depicts, making this handsome marriage of art and science the ideal g Exquisite images from
                award-winning National Geographic photographer Robert Clark offer a captivating perspective on the vast
                beauty and myriad functions of a seemingly simple thing: the bird feather. Each detailed close-up is
                paired with informative text about the utility and evolution of the feather it depicts, making this
                handsome marriage of art and science the ideal gift for bird lovers, natural history buffs, and
                photography enthusiasts. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6161564899ac6d10decca00d60477454</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f2/ee/f2ee668cf593ff13a9560c2801e9c2a2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>7ba1c3c62e5551a8f4a0679ea8fb0687</id>
            <title>Saga, Volume 2 (Saga (Collected Editions) #2)</title>
            <price>11.75</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>2</availability_count>
            <description>From award-winning writer BRIAN K. VAUGHAN (Pride of Baghdad, Ex Machina) and critically
                acclaimed artist FIONA STAPLES (Mystery Society, Done to Death), SAGA is sweeping tale of one young
                family fighting to find their place in the universe. Thanks to her star-crossed parents Marko and Alana,
                newborn baby Hazel has already survived lethal assassins, rampaging armies, and h From award-winning
                writer BRIAN K. VAUGHAN (Pride of Baghdad, Ex Machina) and critically acclaimed artist FIONA STAPLES
                (Mystery Society, Done to Death), SAGA is sweeping tale of one young family fighting to find their place
                in the universe. Thanks to her star-crossed parents Marko and Alana, newborn baby Hazel has already
                survived lethal assassins, rampaging armies, and horrific monsters, but in the cold vastness of outer
                space, the little girl encounters her strangest adventure yet... grandparents.Collects Saga issues #7-12
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/1a/eb/1aeb5d30809ad96d7c323228a2bd23d3.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9c592e50ab5d74b1ea2ff84c1f5b9172</id>
            <title>Catching Jordan (Hundred Oaks)</title>
            <price>50.83</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>ONE OF THE BOYSWhat girl doesn't want to be surrounded by gorgeous jocks day in and day out?
                Jordan Woods isn't just surrounded by hot guys, though-she leads them as the captain and quarterback of
                her high school football team. They all see her as one of the guys and that's just fine. As long as she
                gets her athletic scholarship to a powerhouse university.But everything sh ONE OF THE BOYSWhat girl
                doesn't want to be surrounded by gorgeous jocks day in and day out? Jordan Woods isn't just surrounded
                by hot guys, though-she leads them as the captain and quarterback of her high school football team. They
                all see her as one of the guys and that's just fine. As long as she gets her athletic scholarship to a
                powerhouse university.But everything she's ever worked for is threatened when Ty Green moves to her
                school. Not only is he an amazing QB, but he's also amazingly hot. And for the first time, Jordan's
                feeling vulnerable. Can she keep her head in the game while her heart's on the line? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>316b4899867ffb0d5a3cd904a1c75867</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ad/ac/adac97366586d261feab30bf5220756e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>77a286fb813ee51295cf8f464b2edfae</id>
            <title>Fighting Fate (Fighting #6)</title>
            <price>39.24</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>***BONUS CONTENT: The first two chapters of JB Salsbury's stand alone novel SPLIT
                included!Axelle’s broken.I live to hold her together.Killian McCreery only has two dreams . . .Fight for
                the UFL.And Axelle.He’s watched her give her time and her body to men who don’t deserve to breathe her
                air. He’s waited, worked hard to become the kind of man she deserves, hoping one day, ***BONUS CONTENT:
                The first two chapters of JB Salsbury's stand alone novel SPLIT included!Axelle’s broken.I live to hold
                her together.Killian McCreery only has two dreams . . .Fight for the UFL.And Axelle.He’s watched her
                give her time and her body to men who don’t deserve to breathe her air. He’s waited, worked hard to
                become the kind of man she deserves, hoping one day, when the time is right, he’d get the opportunity to
                make her happy. After a painful anniversary, he finally gets his chance.But life has a way of
                sucker-punching its victims—striking when they least expect it in the most devastating ways.Killian
                loves me.But I screwed up. Big time.Axelle Daniels appears to be the typical college student—parties,
                hangovers, and men. No one knows that inside she’s a mess, and no amount of booze or meaningless
                relationships have managed to fill the cracks in her heart. But Killian knows. He’s been there since the
                night it all began and has never left her side.When she wakes up one morning to find the consequences of
                her actions have caught up to her, even Killian’s white-knighthood can’t save her now.Fate is put to the
                test when, for the first time in their five-year friendship, they no longer have each other to lean on.
                When he becomes a UFL superstar, she hardly recognizes the man he used to be. And she no longer needs
                him to hold her together.With the foundation of their friendship gone, they’ll discover that even a love
                that is meant to be needs to be fought for and destiny is a choice. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/57/e2/57e255929f6e597c18cb3843904cd92b.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>972e2e7f25433905a3ed724c80411719</id>
            <title>Burning</title>
            <price>28.81</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>After three years in juvie, Angela Davis is just a few months shy of release, and she'll
                finally be free from the hole that is Brunesfield Correctional Facility. Then Jessica arrives. Only ten
                years old and under the highest security possible, this girl has to be dangerous, even if no one knows
                what she did to land in juvie. As strange things begin happening to Angela and After three years in
                juvie, Angela Davis is just a few months shy of release, and she'll finally be free from the hole that
                is Brunesfield Correctional Facility. Then Jessica arrives. Only ten years old and under the highest
                security possible, this girl has to be dangerous, even if no one knows what she did to land in juvie. As
                strange things begin happening to Angela and her friends that can only be traced to the new girl's
                arrival, it becomes clear that Brunesfield is no longer safe. They must find a way to get out, but how
                can they save themselves when the world has forgotten them? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>316b4899867ffb0d5a3cd904a1c75867</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/26/95/269507c7bb35d2cec9b61a03d1c28e67.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9de19061945ab39f48e953a0c7d44366</id>
            <title>A Distant Mirror: The Calamitous 14th Century</title>
            <price>14.58</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>Barbara W. Tuchman--the acclaimed author of the Pulitzer Prize–winning classic The Guns of
                August--once again marshals her gift for character, history, and sparkling prose to compose an
                astonishing portrait of medieval Europe.The fourteenth century reflects two contradictory images: on the
                one hand, a glittering age of crusades, cathedrals, and chivalry; on the other, a wo Barbara W.
                Tuchman--the acclaimed author of the Pulitzer Prize–winning classic The Guns of August--once again
                marshals her gift for character, history, and sparkling prose to compose an astonishing portrait of
                medieval Europe.The fourteenth century reflects two contradictory images: on the one hand, a glittering
                age of crusades, cathedrals, and chivalry; on the other, a world plunged into chaos and spiritual agony.
                In this revelatory work, Tuchman examines not only the great rhythms of history but the grain and
                texture of domestic life: what childhood was like; what marriage meant; how money, taxes, and war
                dominated the lives of serf, noble, and clergy alike. Granting her subjects their loyalties,
                treacheries, and guilty passions, Tuchman re-creates the lives of proud cardinals, university scholars,
                grocers and clerks, saints and mystics, lawyers and mercenaries, and, dominating all, the knight--in all
                his valor and “furious follies,” a “terrible worm in an iron cocoon.” ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>115c4bb892c6e92e7300d57d705e7314</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/41/d5/41d5fa6a81cdbcbe6b0b15757a4c9144.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>77637d4d2fed86040ba2e109874ad449</id>
            <title>Extreme Prey (Lucas Davenport #26)</title>
            <price>25.4</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>The extraordinary new Lucas Davenport thriller from #1New York Times–bestselling author and
                Pulitzer Prize winner John Sandford. After the events in Gathering Prey, Lucas Davenport finds himself
                in a very unusual situation—no longer employed by the Minnesota BCA. His friend the governor is just
                cranking up a presidential campaign, though, and he invites Lucas to come alon The extraordinary new
                Lucas Davenport thriller from #1 New York Times–bestselling author and Pulitzer Prize winner John
                Sandford.   After the events in Gathering Prey, Lucas Davenport finds himself in a very unusual
                situation—no longer employed by the Minnesota BCA. His friend the governor is just cranking up a
                presidential campaign, though, and he invites Lucas to come along as part of his campaign staff. “Should
                be fun!” he says, and it kind of is—until they find they have a shadow: an armed man intent on killing
                the governor . . . and anyone who gets in the way. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>280a530c4c5e7c6d9f5e2ef32cdf82d6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/de/86/de86d4f1563fad2ca088922fbbb2b36a.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5f33b1c5053dcee0fca57b6d10d39bf1</id>
            <title>The Name of the Wind (The Kingkiller Chronicle #1)</title>
            <price>50.59</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Told in Kvothe's own voice, this is the tale of the magically gifted young man who grows to be
                the most notorious wizard his world has ever seen. The intimate narrative of his childhood in a troupe
                of traveling players, his years spent as a near-feral orphan in a crime-ridden city, his daringly brazen
                yet successful bid to enter a legendary school of magic, and his life as Told in Kvothe's own voice,
                this is the tale of the magically gifted young man who grows to be the most notorious wizard his world
                has ever seen. The intimate narrative of his childhood in a troupe of traveling players, his years spent
                as a near-feral orphan in a crime-ridden city, his daringly brazen yet successful bid to enter a
                legendary school of magic, and his life as a fugitive after the murder of a king form a gripping
                coming-of-age story unrivaled in recent literature. A high-action story written with a poet's hand, The
                Name of the Wind is a masterpiece that will transport readers into the body and mind of a wizard.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/6a/b3/6ab3616e7495ef64b1546a178cf8a9e7.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f6ac197bdeb623a6da748350c7e45b20</id>
            <title>Orchestra of Exiles: The Story of Bronislaw Huberman, the Israel Philharmonic, and the One Thousand
                Jews He Saved from Nazi Horrors
            </title>
            <price>12.36</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>The compelling biography of the violinist who founded the Palestine Symphony Orchestra and
                saved hundreds of people from Hitler—as seen in Josh Aronson’s documentary Orchestra of Exiles.“The true
                artist does not create art as an end in itself. He creates art for human beings. Humanity is the
                goal.”—Bronislaw HubermanAt fourteen, Bronislaw Huberman played the Brahms Violin The compelling
                biography of the violinist who founded the Palestine Symphony Orchestra and saved hundreds of people
                from Hitler—as seen in Josh Aronson’s documentary Orchestra of Exiles.“The true artist does not create
                art as an end in itself. He creates art for human beings. Humanity is the goal.”—Bronislaw HubermanAt
                fourteen, Bronislaw Huberman played the Brahms Violin Concerto in Vienna— winning high praise from the
                composer himself, who was there. Instantly famous, Huberman began touring all over the world and
                received invitations to play for royalty across Europe. But after witnessing the tragedy of World War I,
                he committed his phenomenal talent and celebrity to aid humanity.After studying at the Sorbonne in
                Paris, Huberman joined the ranks of Sigmund Freud and Albert Einstein in calling for peace through the
                Pan European Movement. But when hope for their noble vision was destroyed by the rise of Nazism,
                Huberman began a crusade that would become his greatest legacy—the creation, in 1936, of the Palestine
                Symphony, which twelve years later became the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra.In creating this world-level
                orchestra, Huberman miraculously arranged for the very best Jewish musicians and their families to
                emigrate from Nazi-threatened territories. His tireless campaigning for the project—including a marathon
                fundraising concert tour across America—ultimately saved nearly a thousand Jews from the approaching
                Holocaust. Inviting the great Arturo Toscanini to conduct the orchestra’s first concert, Huberman’s
                clarion call of art over cruelty was heard around the world. His story contains estraordinary
                adventures, riches and royalty, politicians and broken promises, losses and triumphs. Against near
                impossible obstacles, Huberman refused to give up on his dream to create a unique and life-saving
                orchestra of exiles which was one of the great cultural achievements of the 20th century.Includes
                Photographs ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>a9a8dcfa66cfe6d431ed158c72efd11f</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/15/de/15de75548ee9a4c6be1420ee309c03e0.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>bde31e243f9055be2f954fbc3615e77d</id>
            <title>The Drowning Girls</title>
            <price>35.67</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>Critically acclaimed author of The Mourning Hours and The Fragile World, Paula Treick DeBoard
                returns with a tale of dark secrets, shocking lies and a dangerous obsession that will change one
                neighborhood forever.Liz McGinnis never imagined herself living in a luxurious gated community like The
                Palms. Ever since she and her family moved in, she's felt like an outsider amon Critically acclaimed
                author of The Mourning Hours and The Fragile World, Paula Treick DeBoard returns with a tale of dark
                secrets, shocking lies and a dangerous obsession that will change one neighborhood forever.Liz McGinnis
                never imagined herself living in a luxurious gated community like The Palms. Ever since she and her
                family moved in, she's felt like an outsider amongst the Stepford-like wives and their obnoxiously
                spoiled children. Still, she's determined to make it work—if not for herself, then for her husband,
                Phil, who landed them this lavish home in the first place, and for her daughter, Danielle, who's about
                to enter high school. Yet underneath the glossy veneer of The Palms, life is far from idyllic. In a
                place where reputation is everything, Liz soon discovers that even the friendliest residents can't be
                trusted—and almost everyone has secrets they'd do anything to protect. So when the gorgeous girl next
                door befriends Danielle, Liz can't help but find sophisticated Kelsey's interest in her shy and slightly
                nerdy daughter a bit suspicious. But while Kelsey quickly becomes a fixture in the McGinnis home, Liz's
                relationships with both Danielle and Phil grow strained. Now even her own family seems to be hiding
                things, and it's not long before their dream of living the high life quickly spirals out of control…
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f5/d9/f5d90537f3bed5ad7c8971190beb0730.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>de96f169eecaa6bf281109db9440a5ef</id>
            <title>The New Guy (and Other Senior Year Distractions)</title>
            <price>44.92</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>A ridiculously cute, formerly-famous new guy dropping into your life? It's practically every
                girl's dream. But not Jules McCallister-Morgan's. I realize that on paper I look like your standard
                type-A, neurotic, overachiever. And maybe I am. But I didn't get to be the editor of my school's
                long-revered newspaper by just showing up*. I have one main goal for my senior year-e A ridiculously
                cute, formerly-famous new guy dropping into your life? It's practically every girl's dream. But not
                Jules McCallister-Morgan's. I realize that on paper I look like your standard type-A, neurotic,
                overachiever. And maybe I am. But I didn't get to be the editor of my school's long-revered newspaper by
                just showing up*. I have one main goal for my senior year-early acceptance into my first choice Ivy
                League college-and I will not be deterred by best friends, moms who think I could stand to "live a
                little," or boys. At least, that was the plan before I knew about Alex Powell**.And before Alex Powell
                betrayed me***.I know what you're thinking: Calm down, Jules. But you don't understand. This stuff
                matters. This is my life. And I'm not going down without a fight. ----* Okay, I sort of did. But it's a
                sore subject.** I mean, I guess everyone knows about Alex Powell? Two years ago, you couldn't go
                anywhere without hearing about viral video boy band sensation Chaos 4 All. Two years ago, Alex Powell
                was famous.***Some people think I'm overreacting. But this. Means. War.Filled with romance, rivalry, and
                passive-aggressive dog walking, Amy Spalding delivers a hilariously relatable high school story that's
                sure to have you falling for The New Guy. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>316b4899867ffb0d5a3cd904a1c75867</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/d8/9d/d89dc869d5ea1462fd746ac6de97583f.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>b259d2abb42311120bd033d05e81967d</id>
            <title>Better Homes and Gardens New Cook Book</title>
            <price>39.61</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>6</availability_count>
            <description>Features: Over 900 new recipes -- 1,200 in all-reflect current eating habits and lifestyles;
                500 new photographs -- over 700 in all-including 60 percent more of finished food than the last edition;
                Dozens of new recipes offer ethnic flavours, fresh ingredients, or vegetarian appeal; Many recipes
                feature make-ahead directions or quick-to-the-table meals; New chapter provide Features: Over 900 new
                recipes -- 1,200 in all-reflect current eating habits and lifestyles; 500 new photographs -- over 700 in
                all-including 60 percent more of finished food than the last edition; Dozens of new recipes offer ethnic
                flavours, fresh ingredients, or vegetarian appeal; Many recipes feature make-ahead directions or
                quick-to-the-table meals; New chapter provides recipes for crockery cookers; Efficient, easy-to-read
                format, with recipes categorised into 21 chapters, each thoroughly indexed for easy reference; Expanded
                chapter on cooking basics includes advice on food safety, menu planning, table setting, and make-ahead
                cooking, plus a thorough glossary on ingredients and techniques; Appliance-friendly recipes help cooks
                save time and creatively use new kitchen tools; Nutrition information with each recipe, plus diabetic
                exchanges; Contemporary food photography attracts browsers and helps cooks discover new recipes to make;
                Icons identify low-fat, no-fat, fast, and best-loved recipes; Every recipe tested and perfected by the
                Better Homes and Gardens Test Kitchen; Revised and updated cooking charts, ingredient photos, emergency
                substitutions, and equivalents; Respected, reliable kitchen reference with hundreds of cooking terms,
                tips, and techniques. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>29e4a3e5b5a3c7fa2cdb4779729a375c</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/75/82/7582e20b84f603358a8d55cd6a0a50f4.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>b60d38c9359ea14d37e2f250aa3dbfda</id>
            <title>Animal Farm</title>
            <price>57.22</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Tired of their servitude to man, a group of farm animals revolt and establish their own
                society, only to be betrayed into worse servitude by their leaders, the pigs, whose slogan becomes: "All
                animals are equal, but some animals are more equal than others." This 1945 satire addresses the
                socialist/communist philosophy of Stalin in the Soviet Union.
            </description>
            <category_id>8f67479d76bd33a8c33519a169c2184d</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/10/db/10db56354b4550d92270c6f097d9bebc.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>a7186297d92232150ac24f7e9b66a3a6</id>
            <title>Shobu Samurai, Project Aryoku (#3)</title>
            <price>29.06</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>Welcome to the Ark. In a place known as the Six Civilizations all is not as it seems, the six
                leaders though living in peace for the last decade soon find themselves struck by tragedy again! When
                the grandson of Chaos P. Karafuta, the world's infamous scientist and inventor, King and his best friend
                Shabu accidently unlock the secrets to a weapon known simply as ‘Project A Welcome to the Ark. In a
                place known as the Six Civilizations all is not as it seems, the six leaders though living in peace for
                the last decade soon find themselves struck by tragedy again! When the grandson of Chaos P. Karafuta,
                the world's infamous scientist and inventor, King and his best friend Shabu accidently unlock the
                secrets to a weapon known simply as ‘Project Aryoku'. In his greed for power King will sacrifice
                everyone he loves to obtain its power. However, it falls into the hands of his nephew, Shobu Samurai. At
                the sight of losing his parents, his unbound power obliterates his hometown with no recollection of
                doing so. Now ten years later, Shobu Samurai returns to seek revenge on his uncle but instead will face
                a choice to save his home from shadow creatures, blood beast and organization once thought dead. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ae/0c/ae0ccc307568b6d7699786411f3cbcc4.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f19ac18f85283fb17f2ffdbaebdeeb81</id>
            <title>Very Good Lives: The Fringe Benefits of Failure and the Importance of Imagination</title>
            <price>50.66</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>In 2008, J.K. Rowling delivered a deeply affecting commencement speech at Harvard University.
                Now published for the first time in book form, Very Good Lives offers J.K. Rowling’s words of wisdom for
                anyone at a turning point in life, asking the profound and provocative questions: How can we embrace
                failure? And how can we use our imagination to better both ourselves and ot In 2008, J.K. Rowling
                delivered a deeply affecting commencement speech at Harvard University. Now published for the first time
                in book form, Very Good Lives offers J.K. Rowling’s words of wisdom for anyone at a turning point in
                life, asking the profound and provocative questions: How can we embrace failure? And how can we use our
                imagination to better both ourselves and others?Drawing from stories of her own post-graduate years, the
                world-famous author addresses some of life’s most important issues with acuity and emotional force.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ab/ac/abac4222af5cc296b704a0e5df82e162.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>60466b22c415181035a8a72d64c9c376</id>
            <title>Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future</title>
            <price>34.06</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>If you want to build a better future, you must believe in secrets.The great secret of our time
                is that there are still uncharted frontiers to explore and new inventions to create. In Zero to One ,
                legendary entrepreneur and investor Peter Thiel shows how we can find singular ways to create those new
                things. Thiel begins with the contrarian premise that we live in an age o If you want to build a better
                future, you must believe in secrets.The great secret of our time is that there are still uncharted
                frontiers to explore and new inventions to create. In Zero to One , legendary entrepreneur and investor
                Peter Thiel shows how we can find singular ways to create those new things. Thiel begins with the
                contrarian premise that we live in an age of technological stagnation, even if we’re too distracted by
                shiny mobile devices to notice. Information technology has improved rapidly, but there is no reason why
                progress should be limited to computers or Silicon Valley. Progress can be achieved in any industry or
                area of business. It comes from the most important skill that every leader must master: learning to
                think for yourself.Doing what someone else already knows how to do takes the world from 1 to n, adding
                more of something familiar. But when you do something new, you go from 0 to 1. The next Bill Gates will
                not build an operating system. The next Larry Page or Sergey Brin won’t make a search engine. Tomorrow’s
                champions will not win by competing ruthlessly in today’s marketplace. They will escape competition
                altogether, because their businesses will be unique. Zero to One presents at once an optimistic view of
                the future of progress in America and a new way of thinking about innovation: it starts by learning to
                ask the questions that lead you to find value in unexpected places. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f4/8e/f48ee738bc992a68d08eadcb4338a547.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>de2b10ba87eb054a13bfc5197bf93470</id>
            <title>Doing It Over (Most Likely To #1)</title>
            <price>35.61</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>Voted Most Likely to Succeed, Melanie Bartlett ended up anything but. The down-on-her-luck
                single mom wants a complete do-over—is that too much to ask? With her family long gone from River Bend,
                strong, independent Mel is as surprised as anyone to end up in the quaint small town she once called
                home. But with her friends, Jo and Zoe, by her side, and a comfortable room at Voted Most Likely to
                Succeed, Melanie Bartlett ended up anything but. The down-on-her-luck single mom wants a complete
                do-over—is that too much to ask? With her family long gone from River Bend, strong, independent Mel is
                as surprised as anyone to end up in the quaint small town she once called home. But with her friends, Jo
                and Zoe, by her side, and a comfortable room at Miss Gina’s quirky bed-and-breakfast, she just might
                have turned the corner on a new life.Wyatt Gibson never liked the big city. River Bend suits the
                ruggedly handsome builder just fine. Wyatt knows he’s home, even if that means being charmed by the
                appearance of Melanie and her spunky, adorable daughter. Is Wyatt’s calm devotion—even amid a coming
                storm—enough to convince Mel she may have found a home to call her own, a family that never leaves, and
                a true love to last a lifetime? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e9/25/e9250495a525eb203652ad9da85ccb8e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>16bca266c4a5697184b8f1cdf4ef2bba</id>
            <title>The Girl In The Ice (DCI Erika Foster #1)</title>
            <price>15.85</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Her eyes are wide open. Her lips parted as if to speak. Her dead body frozen in the ice…She is
                not the only one. When a young boy discovers the body of a woman beneath a thick sheet of ice in a South
                London park, Detective Erika Foster is called in to lead the murder investigation. The victim, a
                beautiful young socialite, appeared to have the perfect life. Yet when Erika b Her eyes are wide open.
                Her lips parted as if to speak. Her dead body frozen in the ice…She is not the only one. When a young
                boy discovers the body of a woman beneath a thick sheet of ice in a South London park, Detective Erika
                Foster is called in to lead the murder investigation. The victim, a beautiful young socialite, appeared
                to have the perfect life. Yet when Erika begins to dig deeper, she starts to connect the dots between
                the murder and the killings of three prostitutes, all found strangled, hands bound and dumped in water
                around London. What dark secrets is the girl in the ice hiding? As Erika inches closer to uncovering the
                truth, the killer is closing in on Erika. The last investigation Erika led went badly wrong… resulting
                in the death of her husband. With her career hanging by a thread, Erika must now battle her own personal
                demons as well as a killer more deadly than any she’s faced before. But will she get to him before he
                strikes again?A page-turning thriller packed with suspense. If you like Angela Marsons, Rachel Abbott
                and Karin Slaughter, discover Rob Bryndza’s new series today – at a special launch price. Watch out for
                more from DCI Erika FosterShe’s fearless. Respected. Unstoppable. Detective Erika Foster will catch a
                killer, whatever it takes. 1. THE GIRL IN THE ICE 2. THE NIGHT STALKER (COMING SOON) ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>280a530c4c5e7c6d9f5e2ef32cdf82d6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/d8/f7/d8f77fe7f4bb8610e903741441f84702.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>6c7c3b8a1b46ae65f6adda676aa2a502</id>
            <title>Girl, Interrupted</title>
            <price>42.14</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>6</availability_count>
            <description>See alternate cover edition here.In 1967, after a session with a psychiatrist she'd never seen
                before, eighteen-year-old Susanna Kaysen was put in a taxi and sent to McLean Hospital. She spent most
                of the next two years on the ward for teenage girls in a psychiatric hospital as renowned for its famous
                clientele -- Sylvia Plath, Robert Lowell, James Taylor, and Ray Charles See alternate cover edition
                here.In 1967, after a session with a psychiatrist she'd never seen before, eighteen-year-old Susanna
                Kaysen was put in a taxi and sent to McLean Hospital. She spent most of the next two years on the ward
                for teenage girls in a psychiatric hospital as renowned for its famous clientele -- Sylvia Plath, Robert
                Lowell, James Taylor, and Ray Charles -- as for its progressive methods of treating those who could
                afford its sanctuary. Kaysen's memoir encompasses horror and razor-edged perception while providing
                vivid portraits of her fellow patients and their keepers. It is a brilliant evocation of a "parallel
                universe" set within the kaleidoscopically shifting landscape of the late sixties. Girl, Interrupted is
                a clear-sighted, unflinching document that gives lasting and specific dimension to our definitions of
                sane and insane, mental illness and recovery. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f9/ec/f9ec97bd8b29cc4e36d6c2b093d04709.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4534e89e2f87d70509059a3c2422b20a</id>
            <title>Data, A Love Story: How I Gamed Online Dating to Meet My Match</title>
            <price>32.35</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>Forty million people date online each year. Most don’t find true love. Thanks to Data, a Love
                Story, their odds just got a whole lot better. Data, A Love Story: How I Gamed Online Dating to Meet My
                Match is a lively, thought-provoking memoir about how one woman “gamed” the world of online dating—and
                met her eventual husband.
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/1f/d8/1fd8340d9b3fd95861f0407b4dbb0fa7.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>02f767a03fae9bd5c100653ba45dfc20</id>
            <title>It Didn't Start with You: How Inherited Family Trauma Shapes Who We Are and How to End the Cycle
            </title>
            <price>56.27</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>A groundbreaking approach to transforming traumatic legacies passed down in families over
                generations, by an acclaimed expert in the field Depression. Anxiety. Chronic Pain. Phobias. Obsessive
                thoughts. The evidence is compelling: the roots of these difficulties may not reside in our immediate
                life experience or in chemical imbalances in our brains—but in the lives of our A groundbreaking
                approach to transforming traumatic legacies passed down in families over generations, by an acclaimed
                expert in the field  Depression. Anxiety. Chronic Pain. Phobias. Obsessive thoughts. The evidence is
                compelling: the roots of these difficulties may not reside in our immediate life experience or in
                chemical imbalances in our brains—but in the lives of our parents, grandparents, and even
                great-grandparents. The latest scientific research, now making headlines, supports what many have long
                intuited—that traumatic experience can be passed down through generations. It Didn’t Start with You
                builds on the work of leading experts in post-traumatic stress, including Mount Sinai School of Medicine
                neuroscientist Rachel Yehuda and psychiatrist Bessel van der Kolk, author of The Body Keeps the Score.
                Even if the person who suffered the original trauma has died, or the story has been forgotten or
                silenced, memory and feelings can live on. These emotional legacies are often hidden, encoded in
                everything from gene expression to everyday language, and they play a far greater role in our emotional
                and physical health than has ever before been understood.   As a pioneer in the field of inherited
                family trauma, Mark Wolynn has worked with individuals and groups on a therapeutic level for over twenty
                years. It Didn’t Start with You offers a pragmatic and prescriptive guide to his method, the Core
                Language Approach. Diagnostic self-inventories provide a way to uncover the fears and anxieties conveyed
                through everyday words, behaviors, and physical symptoms. Techniques for developing a genogram or
                extended family tree create a map of experiences going back through the generations. And visualization,
                active imagination, and direct dialogue create pathways to reconnection, integration, and reclaiming
                life and health. It Didn’t Start With You is a transformative approach to resolving longstanding
                difficulties that in many cases, traditional therapy, drugs, or other interventions have not had the
                capacity to touch. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>94579d5666d9575b6b2e6130d00c60b5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ee/a9/eea9e831f8964b4dc0190c84a1f9a1f6.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>67703da3f6d54476ff6692b1c458b911</id>
            <title>Benjamin Franklin: An American Life</title>
            <price>48.19</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>Benjamin Franklin is the Founding Father who winks at us. An ambitious urban entrepreneur who
                rose up the social ladder, from leather-aproned shopkeeper to dining with kings, he seems made of flesh
                rather than of marble. In bestselling author Walter Isaacson's vivid and witty full-scale biography, we
                discover why Franklin seems to turn to us from history's stage with eyes Benjamin Franklin is the
                Founding Father who winks at us. An ambitious urban entrepreneur who rose up the social ladder, from
                leather-aproned shopkeeper to dining with kings, he seems made of flesh rather than of marble. In
                bestselling author Walter Isaacson's vivid and witty full-scale biography, we discover why Franklin
                seems to turn to us from history's stage with eyes that twinkle from behind his new-fangled spectacles.
                By bringing Franklin to life, Isaacson shows how he helped to define both his own time and ours. He was,
                during his 84-year life, America's best scientist, inventor, diplomat, writer, and business strategist,
                and he was also one of its most practical -- though not most profound -- political thinkers. He proved
                by flying a kite that lightning was electricity, and he invented a rod to tame it. He sought practical
                ways to make stoves less smoky and commonwealths less corrupt. He organized neighborhood constabularies
                and international alliances, local lending libraries and national legislatures. He combined two types of
                lenses to create bifocals and two concepts of representation to foster the nation's federal compromise.
                He was the only man who shaped all the founding documents of America: the Albany Plan of Union, the
                Declaration of Independence, the treaty of alliance with France, the peace treaty with England, and the
                Constitution. And he helped invent America's unique style of homespun humor, democratic values, and
                philosophical pragmatism. But the most interesting thing that Franklin invented, and continually
                reinvented, was himself. America's first great publicist, he was, in his life and in his writings,
                consciously trying to create a new American archetype. In the process, he carefully crafted his own
                persona, portrayed it in public, and polished it for posterity. Through it all, he trusted the hearts
                and minds of his fellow "leather-aprons" more than he did those of any inbred elite. He saw middle-class
                values as a source of social strength, not as something to be derided. His guiding principle was a
                "dislike of everything that tended to debase the spirit of the common people." Few of his fellow
                founders felt this comfort with democracy so fully, and none so intuitively. In this colorful and
                intimate narrative, Isaacson provides the full sweep of Franklin's amazing life, from his days as a
                runaway printer to his triumphs as a statesman, scientist, and Founding Father. He chronicles Franklin's
                tumultuous relationship with his illegitimate son and grandson, his practical marriage, and his
                flirtations with the ladies of Paris. He also shows how Franklin helped to create the American character
                and why he has a particular resonance in the twenty-first century. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>b942462de516c69a778d56ccae99fd15</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/25/f8/25f869fa75340fca0fc2a68e8a0412a1.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>1c5e4ab4fede7212e5873b8ac1dcfbfa</id>
            <title>Every Last Word</title>
            <price>46.47</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>If you could read my mind, you wouldn't be smiling.Samantha McAllister looks just like the rest
                of the popular girls in her junior class. But hidden beneath the straightened hair and expertly applied
                makeup is a secret that her friends would never understand: Sam has Purely-Obsessional OCD and is
                consumed by a stream of dark thoughts and worries that she can't turn off. Se If you could read my mind,
                you wouldn't be smiling.Samantha McAllister looks just like the rest of the popular girls in her junior
                class. But hidden beneath the straightened hair and expertly applied makeup is a secret that her friends
                would never understand: Sam has Purely-Obsessional OCD and is consumed by a stream of dark thoughts and
                worries that she can't turn off. Second-guessing every move, thought, and word makes daily life a
                struggle, and it doesn't help that her lifelong friends will turn toxic at the first sign of a wrong
                outfit, wrong lunch, or wrong crush. Yet Sam knows she'd be truly crazy to leave the protection of the
                most popular girls in school. So when Sam meets Caroline, she has to keep her new friend with a
                refreshing sense of humor and no style a secret, right up there with Sam's weekly visits to her
                psychiatrist.Caroline introduces Sam to Poet's Corner, a hidden room and a tight-knit group of misfits
                who have been ignored by the school at large. Sam is drawn to them immediately, especially a
                guitar-playing guy with a talent for verse, and starts to discover a whole new side of herself. Slowly,
                she begins to feel more "normal" than she ever has as part of the popular crowd . . . until she finds a
                new reason to question her sanity and all she holds dear. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/92/e7/92e7f0a8ca38964fea93e911aefbf6c9.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9b8f42707dd2f37a3734875dcad3fa78</id>
            <title>The 10% Entrepreneur: Live Your Startup Dream Without Quitting Your Day Job</title>
            <price>27.55</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>Choosing between the stability of a traditional career and the upside of entrepreneurship? Why
                not have both?Becoming a full-time entrepreneur can look glamorous from the outside. Who doesn’t want to
                chase their dreams, be their own boss, and do what they love? But the truth is that entrepreneurship is
                often a slog, with no regular hours, no job security, and very little p Choosing between the stability
                of a traditional career and the upside of entrepreneurship? Why not have both?Becoming a full-time
                entrepreneur can look glamorous from the outside. Who doesn’t want to chase their dreams, be their own
                boss, and do what they love? But the truth is that entrepreneurship is often a slog, with no regular
                hours, no job security, and very little pay.  What if there was a way to have the stability of a day job
                with the excitement of a startup? All of the benefits of entrepreneurship with none of the pitfalls? In
                The 10% Entrepreneur, Patrick McGinnis shows you how, by investing just 10% of your time and resources,
                you can become an entrepreneur without losing a steady paycheck.  McGinnis details a step-by-step plan
                that takes you from identifying your first entrepreneurial project to figuring out the smartest way to
                commit resources to it. He shows you how to select and engage in projects that will provide you with
                upside outside the office while making your better at your day job. He also profiles real-world 10%
                Entrepreneurs such as...•Luke Holden, a cash-strapped recent college graduate, who started his own
                lobster-roll empire and oversaw much of its first year of operations, all while working full time in
                corporate America•Dipali Patwa, a designer and mom whose side project designing and selling infant
                clothing is now a sensation.•A group of friends who met at a 6am Bible study class and went on to start
                a brewery that now generates millions in sales . A successful 10% Entrepreneur himself, McGinnis
                explains the multiple paths you can follow to invest your cash, time, and expertise in a
                start-up—including as a founder, angel, adviser, or aficionado. Most importantly, you don’t have to have
                millions in disposable income to become a 10% Entrepreneur. When you put McGinnis’s 10% principles into
                action, you’ll quickly start racking up small wins, then watch as they snowball into your new (and far
                more entrepreneurial) life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>383351f1704abf38d77ea6ea4bac1fd5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/82/93/82939ca78da0b724f16ec814849514fd.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>efbf5dfa6cf0e97b1d9e6be7525c05d8</id>
            <title>Last One Home (New Beginnings #1)</title>
            <price>59.98</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>Growing up, Cassie Carter and her sisters, Karen and Nichole, were incredibly close -- until
                one fateful event drove them apart. After high school, Cassie ran away from home to marry the wrong man,
                throwing away a college scholarship and breaking her parents’ hearts. To make matters worse, Cassie had
                always been their father’s favorite -- a sentiment that weighed heavily o Growing up, Cassie Carter and
                her sisters, Karen and Nichole, were incredibly close -- until one fateful event drove them apart. After
                high school, Cassie ran away from home to marry the wrong man, throwing away a college scholarship and
                breaking her parents’ hearts. To make matters worse, Cassie had always been their father’s favorite -- a
                sentiment that weighed heavily on her sisters and made Cassie’s actions even harder to bear.Now
                thirty-one, Cassie is back in Washington, living in Seattle with her daughter and hoping to leave her
                past behind. After ending a difficult marriage, Cassie is back on her own two feet, the pieces of her
                life slowly but surely coming together. Despite the strides Cassie’s made, she hasn’t been able to make
                peace with her sisters. Karen, the oldest, is a busy wife and mother, balancing her career with raising
                her two children. And Nichole, the youngest, is a stay-at-home mom whose husband indulges her every
                whim. Then one day, Cassie receives a letter from Karen, offering what Cassie thinks may be a chance to
                reconcile. And as Cassie opens herself up to new possibilities -- making amends with her sisters,
                finding love once more -- she realizes the power of compassion, and the promise of a fresh start.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e4/0a/e40a336622fe578699be5a1eeba18f9d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d8b268f50ae991823cd391e96db2162b</id>
            <title>Stiff: The Curious Lives of Human Cadavers</title>
            <price>36.74</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Stiff is an oddly compelling, often hilarious exploration of the strange lives of our bodies
                postmortem. For two thousand years, cadavers—some willingly, some unwittingly—have been involved in
                science's boldest strides and weirdest undertakings. In this fascinating account, Mary Roach visits the
                good deeds of cadavers over the centuries and tells the engrossing story of ou Stiff is an oddly
                compelling, often hilarious exploration of the strange lives of our bodies postmortem. For two thousand
                years, cadavers—some willingly, some unwittingly—have been involved in science's boldest strides and
                weirdest undertakings. In this fascinating account, Mary Roach visits the good deeds of cadavers over
                the centuries and tells the engrossing story of our bodies when we are no longer with them. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a0/a0/a0a013b029130df92073f547df83ee5c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d1caa25b6167397dd9ba40c2a011a9b4</id>
            <title>The Girl with All the Gifts</title>
            <price>49.47</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Melanie is a very special girl. Dr. Caldwell calls her "our little genius."Every morning,
                Melanie waits in her cell to be collected for class. When they come for her, Sergeant Parks keeps his
                gun pointing at her while two of his people strap her into the wheelchair. She thinks they don't like
                her. She jokes that she won't bite, but they don't laugh.Melanie loves school. Sh Melanie is a very
                special girl. Dr. Caldwell calls her "our little genius."Every morning, Melanie waits in her cell to be
                collected for class. When they come for her, Sergeant Parks keeps his gun pointing at her while two of
                his people strap her into the wheelchair. She thinks they don't like her. She jokes that she won't bite,
                but they don't laugh.Melanie loves school. She loves learning about spelling and sums and the world
                outside the classroom and the children's cells. She tells her favorite teacher all the things she'll do
                when she grows up. Melanie doesn't know why this makes Miss Justineau look sad. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>1cf5299dd4b5deb500079f922c5c591b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/41/c7/41c74d82b853606fe98182c417b4669c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f2c8db2c62cde24456472ade1a78e54d</id>
            <title>Hawkeye, Vol. 1: My Life as a Weapon (Hawkeye #1)</title>
            <price>45.24</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>The breakout star of this summer's blockbuster Avengers film, Clint Barton - aka the self-made
                hero Hawkeye - fights for justice! With ex-Young Avenger Kate Bishop by his side, he's out to prove
                himself as one of Earth's Mightiest Heroes! SHIELD recruits Clint to intercept a packet of incriminating
                evidence - before he becomes the most wanted man in the world. You won't be The breakout star of this
                summer's blockbuster Avengers film, Clint Barton - aka the self-made hero Hawkeye - fights for justice!
                With ex-Young Avenger Kate Bishop by his side, he's out to prove himself as one of Earth's Mightiest
                Heroes! SHIELD recruits Clint to intercept a packet of incriminating evidence - before he becomes the
                most wanted man in the world. You won't believe what is on The Tape! What is the Vagabond Code? Matt
                Fraction pens a Hawkeye thriller that spans the globe...and the darkest parts of Hawkeye's mind. Barton
                and Bishop mean double the Hawkeye and double the trouble...and stealing from the rich never looked so
                good.COLLECTING: Hawkeye 1-5, Young Avengers Presents 6 ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/16/46/16460146a1a8b99c82da027368383ade.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>c90bf6c2c0fa5924e0768dd85705e5f6</id>
            <title>Playing with Fire</title>
            <price>13.71</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>A beautiful violinist is haunted by a very old piece of music she finds in a strange antique
                shop in Rome.The first time Julia Ansdell picks up The Incendio Waltz, she knows it’s a strikingly
                unusual composition. But while playing the piece, Julia blacks out and awakens to find her young
                daughter implicated in acts of surprising violence. And when she travels to Venice to A beautiful
                violinist is haunted by a very old piece of music she finds in a strange antique shop in Rome.The first
                time Julia Ansdell picks up The Incendio Waltz, she knows it’s a strikingly unusual composition. But
                while playing the piece, Julia blacks out and awakens to find her young daughter implicated in acts of
                surprising violence. And when she travels to Venice to find the previous owner of the music, she
                uncovers a dark secret that involves dangerously powerful people—a family who would stop at nothing to
                keep Julia from bringing the truth to light. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>280a530c4c5e7c6d9f5e2ef32cdf82d6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/90/0b/900bd2e60d56b6480a4e8eb2dddb46d6.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4109274d52b298ef2750d05c6f282e65</id>
            <title>Tracing Numbers on a Train</title>
            <price>41.6</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>Start preparing children for classroom success with Tracing Numbers on a Train! This
                educational workbook is filled with pages of giant numbers that make it easy for little hands to learn
                pencil control, followed by pages of small numbers for repetition and motor skill development. The
                illustrated practice pages will keep kids engaged while learning their numbers from 1 to Start preparing
                children for classroom success with Tracing Numbers on a Train! This educational workbook is filled with
                pages of giant numbers that make it easy for little hands to learn pencil control, followed by pages of
                small numbers for repetition and motor skill development. The illustrated practice pages will keep kids
                engaged while learning their numbers from 1 to 30. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/06/a6/06a6cfcf89afd1601cbba1a16cda57fb.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>24d6e1a1066256229d8463d74fa05574</id>
            <title>The Purpose Driven Life: What on Earth Am I Here for?</title>
            <price>37.19</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>A #1 New York Times bestseller, The Purpose Driven Life will help you understand why you are
                alive and reveal God's amazing plan for you both here and now, and for eternity. Rick Warren will guide
                you through a personal forty-day spiritual journey that will transform your answer to life's most
                important question: What on earth am I here for? Knowing God's purpose for creat A #1 New York Times
                bestseller, The Purpose Driven Life will help you understand why you are alive and reveal God's amazing
                plan for you both here and now, and for eternity. Rick Warren will guide you through a personal
                forty-day spiritual journey that will transform your answer to life's most important question: What on
                earth am I here for? Knowing God's purpose for creating you will reduce your stress, focus your energy,
                simplify your decisions, give meaning to your life, and most important, prepare you for eternity. Movie
                stars and political leaders aren't the only ones turning to Rick Warren for spiritual guidance. Millions
                of people from NBA and LPGA players to corporate executives to high school students to prison inmates
                meet regularly to discuss The Purpose Driven Life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/95/08/9508e6b28fe4c63e67b3ef33f11eff98.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4716deb57a50ff890778be628211f96c</id>
            <title>Luis Paints the World</title>
            <price>53.95</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>Luis wishes Nico wasn't leaving for the Army. To show Nico he doesn't need to go, Luis begins a
                mural on the alleyway wall. Their house, the river, the Parque de las Ardillas—it's the world, all right
                there. Won't Nico miss Mami's sweet flan? What about their baseball games in the street? But as Luis
                awaits his brother's return from duty, his own world expands as well, thr Luis wishes Nico wasn't
                leaving for the Army. To show Nico he doesn't need to go, Luis begins a mural on the alleyway wall.
                Their house, the river, the Parque de las Ardillas—it's the world, all right there. Won't Nico miss
                Mami's sweet flan? What about their baseball games in the street? But as Luis awaits his brother's
                return from duty, his own world expands as well, through swooping paint and the help of their bustling
                Dominican neighborhood. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/85/e7/85e75d5a9309da5807c82decf3d90263.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>72bfdb23972bfb19ef868cd8f060faa4</id>
            <title>Take Me Home Tonight (Rock Star Romance #3)</title>
            <price>53.98</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>A rocker gets a taste of unexpected passion in the latest red-hot Rock Star Romance from the
                award-winning author of I Want You to Want Me. Calix Bourbon might seem like a free spirit, but that’s
                all a front. In reality he’s just trying to keep his fractured family together while working as a
                session musician. When Blue Fire hires him to replace their keyboardist, Calix i A rocker gets a taste
                of unexpected passion in the latest red-hot Rock Star Romance from the award-winning author of I Want
                You to Want Me.   Calix Bourbon might seem like a free spirit, but that’s all a front. In reality he’s
                just trying to keep his fractured family together while working as a session musician. When Blue Fire
                hires him to replace their keyboardist, Calix is determined to make the most of the opportunity—but he
                can’t help being distracted by the band’s sexy personal chef.   Mimi’s temporary gig is great, but she
                has her heart set on auditioning for a televised cooking show. There’s just one problem: she only has a
                week to acquire the skills necessary to survive the competition. Luckily, the band’s new keyboard player
                can teach her exactly what she needs, in the kitchen and in the bedroom... ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a6/4b/a64b3c559f59748bfdbbe75be3e16075.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4b4dcade937d9cbaf92b2bb0b29c1ad4</id>
            <title>It</title>
            <price>25.01</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>To the children, the town was their whole world. To the adults, knowing better, Derry, Maine
                was just their home town: familiar, well-ordered for the most part. A good place to live.It was the
                children who saw - and felt - what made Derry so horribly different. In the storm drains, in the sewers,
                IT lurked, taking on the shape of every nightmare, each one's deepest dread. To the children, the town
                was their whole world. To the adults, knowing better, Derry, Maine was just their home town: familiar,
                well-ordered for the most part. A good place to live.It was the children who saw - and felt - what made
                Derry so horribly different. In the storm drains, in the sewers, IT lurked, taking on the shape of every
                nightmare, each one's deepest dread. Sometimes IT reached up, seizing, tearing, killing . . .The adults,
                knowing better, knew nothing.Time passed and the children grew up, moved away. The horror of IT was
                deep-buried, wrapped in forgetfulness. Until they were called back, once more to confront IT as IT
                stirred and coiled in the sullen depths of their memories, reaching up again to make their past
                nightmares a terrible present reality. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>1cf5299dd4b5deb500079f922c5c591b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f7/b7/f7b73392b12909a1e8261ef3f96c5fd1.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e5bcf2330d9b86c4359dac2d3aaafc9e</id>
            <title>Hush, Hush (Hush, Hush #1)</title>
            <price>47.02</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>A SACRED OATHA FALLEN ANGELA FORBIDDEN LOVERomance was not part of Nora Grey's plan. She's
                never been particularly attracted to the boys at her school, no matter how hard her best friend, Vee,
                pushes them at her. Not until Patch comes along. With his easy smile and eyes that seem to see inside
                her, Patch draws Nora to him against her better judgment.But after a series of t A SACRED OATHA FALLEN
                ANGELA FORBIDDEN LOVERomance was not part of Nora Grey's plan. She's never been particularly attracted
                to the boys at her school, no matter how hard her best friend, Vee, pushes them at her. Not until Patch
                comes along. With his easy smile and eyes that seem to see inside her, Patch draws Nora to him against
                her better judgment.But after a series of terrifying encounters, Nora's not sure whom to trust. Patch
                seems to be everywhere she is and seems to know more about her than her closest friends. She can't
                decide whether she should fall into his arms or run and hide. And when she tries to seek some answers,
                she finds herself near a truth that is way more unsettling than anything Patch makes her feel.For she is
                right in the middle of an ancient battle between the immortal and those that have fallen - and, when it
                comes to choosing sides, the wrong choice will cost Nora her life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/2a/b9/2ab91479fe480e964f319fa8ac6991b2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d4e94b7dbea790829864fd3fe2967c90</id>
            <title>Throne of Glass (Throne of Glass #1)</title>
            <price>35.07</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>An alternate cover edition can be found here.After serving out a year of hard labor in the salt
                mines of Endovier for her crimes, 18-year-old assassin Celaena Sardothien is dragged before the Crown
                Prince. Prince Dorian offers her her freedom on one condition: she must act as his champion in a
                competition to find a new royal assassin.Her opponents are men-thieves and assas An alternate cover
                edition can be found here.After serving out a year of hard labor in the salt mines of Endovier for her
                crimes, 18-year-old assassin Celaena Sardothien is dragged before the Crown Prince. Prince Dorian offers
                her her freedom on one condition: she must act as his champion in a competition to find a new royal
                assassin.Her opponents are men-thieves and assassins and warriors from across the empire, each sponsored
                by a member of the king's council. If she beats her opponents in a series of eliminations, she'll serve
                the kingdom for four years and then be granted her freedom. Celaena finds her training sessions with the
                captain of the guard, Westfall, challenging and exhilirating. But she's bored stiff by court life.
                Things get a little more interesting when the prince starts to show interest in her... but it's the
                gruff Captain Westfall who seems to understand her best.Then one of the other contestants turns up
                dead... quickly followed by another. Can Celaena figure out who the killer is before she becomes a
                victim? As the young assassin investigates, her search leads her to discover a greater destiny than she
                could possibly have imagined. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/32/d6/32d6aa560e8ddf2a4da1526b95d4c7ab.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>ba438248acc3e62a4fc1486593093244</id>
            <title>Tell the Wind and Fire</title>
            <price>45.51</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>In a city divided between opulent luxury in the Light and fierce privations in the Dark, a
                determined young woman survives by guarding her secrets. Lucie Manette was born in the Dark half of the
                city, but careful manipulations won her a home in the Light, celebrity status, and a rich, loving
                boyfriend. Now she just wants to keep her head down, but her boyfriend has a dark In a city divided
                between opulent luxury in the Light and fierce privations in the Dark, a determined young woman survives
                by guarding her secrets. Lucie Manette was born in the Dark half of the city, but careful manipulations
                won her a home in the Light, celebrity status, and a rich, loving boyfriend. Now she just wants to keep
                her head down, but her boyfriend has a dark secret of his own—one involving an apparent stranger who is
                destitute and despised.Lucie alone knows of the deadly connection the young men share, and even as the
                knowledge leads her to make a grave mistake, she can trust no one with the truth.Blood and secrets alike
                spill out when revolution erupts. With both halves of the city burning, and mercy nowhere to be found,
                can Lucie save either boy—or herself?Celebrated author Sarah Rees Brennan tells a magical tale of
                romance and revolution, love and loss. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/3b/0c/3b0c5f4df26b73659af4e25107499384.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>30614377efb36ccb2489210cce04def4</id>
            <title>The Bone Hunters (Lexy Vaughan &amp; Steven Macaulay #2)</title>
            <price>59.71</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>The award-winning author of Valhalla brings back archaeologist Lexy Vaughan and retired Air
                Force officer Steve Macaulay, as they race to save a priceless discovery from disappearing forever.… One
                of the greatest archaeological finds of all time, Peking Man, the 780,000-year-old remains of our
                earliest known human ancestor, disappeared during World War II from a cargo shi The award-winning author
                of Valhalla brings back archaeologist Lexy Vaughan and retired Air Force officer Steve Macaulay, as they
                race to save a priceless discovery from disappearing forever.…   One of the greatest archaeological
                finds of all time, Peking Man, the 780,000-year-old remains of our earliest known human ancestor,
                disappeared during World War II from a cargo ship bound for America.   Now the Chinese government is
                fighting to keep a new religion from taking hold—a faith based on the belief that Peking Man is God. And
                they dispatch ruthless operatives to find and destroy the world’s most priceless fossil.   But the U.S.
                government has its own team on the hunt. From the mountains of Bavaria to the jungles of Central America
                and across the vast Pacific, Professor Barnaby Finchem, his brilliant protégé, Lexy Vaughan, and pilot
                Steve Macaulay will brave the wrath of nature and of man to win a race against unbridled tyranny.…
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>2cd19deab9ef0b88bd2181888ebb9bd0</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ee/d4/eed4d5d63d13f0aa86575c90f8ccacb7.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>612b5f835f0c433b00cfea50cf970c5e</id>
            <title>The Power of Habit: Why We Do What We Do in Life and Business</title>
            <price>16.88</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>A young woman walks into a laboratory. Over the past two years, she has transformed almost
                every aspect of her life. She has quit smoking, run a marathon, and been promoted at work. The patterns
                inside her brain, neurologists discover, have fundamentally changed.Marketers at Procter &amp; Gamble
                study videos of people making their beds. They are desperately trying to figur A young woman walks into
                a laboratory. Over the past two years, she has transformed almost every aspect of her life. She has quit
                smoking, run a marathon, and been promoted at work. The patterns inside her brain, neurologists
                discover, have fundamentally changed. Marketers at Procter &amp; Gamble study videos of people making
                their beds. They are desperately trying to figure out how to sell a new product called Febreze, on track
                to be one of the biggest flops in company history. Suddenly, one of them detects a nearly imperceptible
                pattern—and with a slight shift in advertising, Febreze goes on to earn a billion dollars a year. An
                untested CEO takes over one of the largest companies in America. His first order of business is
                attacking a single pattern among his employees—how they approach worker safety—and soon the firm, Alcoa,
                becomes the top performer in the Dow Jones. What do all these people have in common? They achieved
                success by focusing on the patterns that shape every aspect of our lives.  They succeeded by
                transforming habits. In The Power of Habit, award-winning New York Times business reporter Charles
                Duhigg takes us to the thrilling edge of scientific discoveries that explain why habits exist and how
                they can be changed. With penetrating intelligence and an ability to distill vast amounts of information
                into engrossing narratives, Duhigg brings to life a whole new understanding of human nature and its
                potential for transformation.  Along the way we learn why some people and companies struggle to change,
                despite years of trying, while others seem to remake themselves overnight. We visit laboratories where
                neuroscientists explore how habits work and where, exactly, they reside in our brains. We discover how
                the right habits were crucial to the success of Olympic swimmer Michael Phelps, Starbucks CEO Howard
                Schultz, and civil-rights hero Martin Luther King, Jr. We go inside Procter &amp; Gamble, Target
                superstores, Rick Warren’s Saddleback Church, NFL locker rooms, and the nation’s largest hospitals and
                see how implementing so-called keystone habits can earn billions and mean the difference between failure
                and success, life and death. At its core, The Power of Habit contains an exhilarating argument: The key
                to exercising regularly, losing weight, raising exceptional children, becoming more productive, building
                revolutionary companies and social movements, and achieving success is understanding how habits work.
                 Habits aren’t destiny. As Charles Duhigg shows, by harnessing this new science, we can transform our
                businesses, our communities, and our lives. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/52/df/52dfc44f48cf29e7a9e305bcb63e1899.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>62b82054ef563756b640a7797b7400e0</id>
            <title>Remember Me?</title>
            <price>11.48</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>When twenty-eight-year-old Lexi Smart wakes up in a London hospital, she’s in for a big
                surprise. Her teeth are perfect. Her body is toned. Her handbag is Vuitton. Having survived a car
                accident—in a Mercedes no less—Lexi has lost a big chunk of her memory, three years to be exact, and
                she’s about to find out just how much things have changed.Somehow Lexi went from a twent When
                twenty-eight-year-old Lexi Smart wakes up in a London hospital, she’s in for a big surprise. Her teeth
                are perfect. Her body is toned. Her handbag is Vuitton. Having survived a car accident—in a Mercedes no
                less—Lexi has lost a big chunk of her memory, three years to be exact, and she’s about to find out just
                how much things have changed.Somehow Lexi went from a twenty-five-year-old working girl to a corporate
                big shot with a sleek new loft, a personal assistant, a carb-free diet, and a set of glamorous new
                friends. And who is this gorgeous husband—who also happens to be a multimillionaire? With her mind still
                stuck three years in reverse, Lexi greets this brave new world determined to be the person she…well,
                seems to be. That is, until an adorably disheveled architect drops the biggest bombshell of all.Suddenly
                Lexi is scrambling to catch her balance. Her new life, it turns out, comes complete with secrets,
                schemes, and intrigue. How on earth did all this happen? Will she ever remember? And what will happen
                when she does?With the same wicked humor and delicious charm that have won her millions of devoted fans,
                Sophie Kinsella, author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Shopaholic &amp; Baby, returns with an
                irresistible new novel and a fresh new heroine who finds herself in a life-changing and utterly
                hilarious predicament… ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/3f/95/3f9572f94858197e92786b194f0f12df.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e625a0742b3b25261ca1208d1303ff40</id>
            <title>The Bulletproof Diet: Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life</title>
            <price>49.05</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>In his midtwenties, Dave Asprey was a successful Silicon Valley multimillionaire. He also
                weighed 300 pounds, despite the fact that he was doing what doctors recommended: eating 1,800 calories a
                day and working out 90 minutes a day, six times a week. When his excess fat started causing brain fog
                and food cravings sapped his energy and willpower, Asprey turned to the same h In his midtwenties, Dave
                Asprey was a successful Silicon Valley multimillionaire. He also weighed 300 pounds, despite the fact
                that he was doing what doctors recommended: eating 1,800 calories a day and working out 90 minutes a
                day, six times a week. When his excess fat started causing brain fog and food cravings sapped his energy
                and willpower, Asprey turned to the same hacking techniques that made his fortune to "hack" his own
                biology, investing more than $300,000 and 15 years to uncover what was hindering his energy,
                performance, appearance, and happiness. From private brain EEG facilities to remote monasteries in
                Tibet, through radioactive brain scans, blood chemistry work, nervous system testing, and more, he
                explored traditional and alternative technologies to reach his physical and mental prime. The result?
                The Bulletproof Diet, an anti-inflammatory program for hunger-free, rapid weight loss and peak
                performance. The Bulletproof Diet will challenge—and change—the way you think about weight loss and
                wellness. You will skip breakfast, stop counting calories, eat high levels of healthy saturated fat,
                work out and sleep less, and add smart supplements.In doing so, you'll gain energy, build lean muscle,
                and watch the pounds melt off. By ditching traditional "diet" thinking, Asprey went from being
                overweight and sick in his twenties to maintaining a 100-pound weight loss, increasing his IQ, and
                feeling better than ever in his forties. The Bulletproof Diet is your blueprint to a better life.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>e1f247894e1b3443c16bd40b30dde694</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ee/3e/ee3e219d23e73ba71c79b700f183aaed.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e630b5af4620746929a92402410a923f</id>
            <title>Sister Sable (The Mad Queen #1)</title>
            <price>13.33</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>THE FIRST TENET OF THE WIND: Do not get caught.Sister Sable has lived by the first tenet for
                seven years, but when an unexpected accident reveals the runaway nun to the clergy, she is forced to
                embrace the remaining four.THE SECOND TENET OF THE WIND: Win by any means.With the King’s spymaster
                committed to killing her, and his general regretting he didn’t, Sable enters a de THE FIRST TENET OF THE
                WIND: Do not get caught.Sister Sable has lived by the first tenet for seven years, but when an
                unexpected accident reveals the runaway nun to the clergy, she is forced to embrace the remaining
                four.THE SECOND TENET OF THE WIND: Win by any means.With the King’s spymaster committed to killing her,
                and his general regretting he didn’t, Sable enters a deadly game.THE THIRD TENET OF THE WIND: The
                purpose of picking up a blade is to cut the enemy.Scaring them is discretionary.THE FOURTH TENET OF THE
                WIND: Have no preferred weapon. Even so, she likes the axe.THE FIFTH TENET OF THE WIND: Know the way of
                all professions.Prophet, pilot, assassin, spy, Sable will need to call upon all she has learned to
                protect the King’s future from the past. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/2c/89/2c89c4c5528ab4b9101701437953df75.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d2c3c4f8faadbd344880506ad12ce92a</id>
            <title>Robin War</title>
            <price>47.82</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>It’s Robins vs. cops! Robins vs. Robins! Robins vs. Batman! Robins vs. the Court of
                Owls‽Collecting: Robin War 1-2, Grayson 15, Detective Comics 47, We Are Robin... 7, Robin: Son of Batman
                7, Gotham Academy 13, Red Hood/Arsenal 7, &amp; Teen Titans 15
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/45/1d/451d3543022242b8b245793e6b5c26bb.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5b5d002dfda7bcb785e37be4bdd6b7a5</id>
            <title>Cravings: Recipes for What You Want to Eat</title>
            <price>20.5</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>Though she is best known as a supermodel and Sports Illustrated swimsuit covergirl, all Chrissy
                Teigen really wants to do is talk about dinner—the good, the greasy, the good-for-you, and the goof-ups.
                Stylish but brash, witty and big-hearted, Chrissy cooks beautifully, but with the spirit of the amateur.
                In this book, she shows us how to make cooking part of a stylish life Though she is best known as a
                supermodel and Sports Illustrated swimsuit covergirl, all Chrissy Teigen really wants to do is talk
                about dinner—the good, the greasy, the good-for-you, and the goof-ups. Stylish but brash, witty and
                big-hearted, Chrissy cooks beautifully, but with the spirit of the amateur. In this book, she shows us
                how to make cooking part of a stylish lifestyle and how to look good doing it…or at least how to laugh
                at ourselves if we don’t.“The thing that makes me happiest isn’t when people stop me in the street to
                say they saw me in a magazine, but when they say they were inspired to cook because of what I posted on
                Instagram,” Chrissy Teigen says. Despite being a professional Beautiful Person, Teigen took cooking
                classes, runs a popular food blog, and loves connecting her fans with food through her widely followed
                Twitter and Instagram accounts. In this book, she brings her passion for cooking to the forefront.
                Through 100 recipes that range from her mom’s Thai classics to her own creations and dishes taught to
                her by her chef friends, Chrissy will show us how easy it can be to make cooking accessible and fun.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>29e4a3e5b5a3c7fa2cdb4779729a375c</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ae/5c/ae5ca435fb095e374d2c2aa9f7b6f380.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>3fdf1e5b0578f3797aeb4c1e4d8145b1</id>
            <title>Overload: How to Unplug, Unwind, and Unleash Yourself from the Pressure of Stress</title>
            <price>52.15</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>#1 New York Times bestselling author Joyce Meyer shows readers how to become free from the
                burden of stress so that they can achieve God's best for their lives. As technology increases your
                accessibility, it becomes harder to mute the background noise of your life and receive God's guidance.
                Joyce Meyer calls this OVERLOAD, when the demands of your busy life become all-con #1 New York Times
                bestselling author Joyce Meyer shows readers how to become free from the burden of stress so that they
                can achieve God's best for their lives. As technology increases your accessibility, it becomes harder to
                mute the background noise of your life and receive God's guidance. Joyce Meyer calls this OVERLOAD, when
                the demands of your busy life become all-consuming and overwhelming. But to experience the joyful life
                God has planned, you must make time to focus on His Word. Then you'll receive His healing calmness and
                gain the strength to take on life's challenges, from physical ailments to problems in relationships.
                Through the practical advice and Scriptural wisdom in this book, you'll learn how to unplug and free
                yourself from burdens that weigh you down. You'll gain simple, effective tips for better rest and stress
                management and discover the fulfilling life you were meant to lead. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>0f4974973a2a0372613bd44f7f288a17</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/9c/da/9cda4893c7fce0c1c8eaa34fb092aa04.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>2387ef8dedfb6e9d3e6796d4103f1efb</id>
            <title>Three-Martini Lunch</title>
            <price>23.21</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>From the author of the “thrilling” (The Christian Science Monitor) novel The Other Typist comes
                an evocative, multilayered story of ambition, success, and secrecy in 1950s New York. In 1958, Greenwich
                Village buzzes with beatniks, jazz clubs, and new ideas—the ideal spot for three ambitious young people
                to meet. Cliff Nelson, the son of a successful book editor, is convin From the author of the “thrilling”
                (The Christian Science Monitor) novel The Other Typist comes an evocative, multilayered story of
                ambition, success, and secrecy in 1950s New York.   In 1958, Greenwich Village buzzes with beatniks,
                jazz clubs, and new ideas—the ideal spot for three ambitious young people to meet. Cliff Nelson, the son
                of a successful book editor, is convinced he’s the next Kerouac, if only his father would notice. Eden
                Katz dreams of being an editor but is shocked when she encounters roadblocks to that ambition. And Miles
                Tillman, a talented black writer from Harlem, seeks to learn the truth about his father’s past, finding
                love in the process. Though different from one another, all three share a common goal: to succeed in the
                competitive and uncompromising world of book publishing. As they reach for what they want, they come to
                understand what they must sacrifice, conceal, and betray to achieve their goals, learning they must live
                with the consequences of their choices. In Three-Martini Lunch, Suzanne Rindell has written both a
                page-turning morality tale and a captivating look at a stylish, demanding era—and a world steeped in
                tradition that’s poised for great upheaval. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/1d/8e/1d8eb8aaebd14464fc58a681091b8d45.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>44e089fb7e5e9a62c22774da226e9412</id>
            <title>Patience</title>
            <price>10.16</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>Patience is a psychedelic science-fiction love story, veering with uncanny precision from
                violent destruction to deeply personal tenderness in a way that is both quintessentially “Clowesian” and
                utterly unique in the author’s body of work. This 180-page, full-color original graphic novel affords
                Clowes the opportunity to draw some of the most exuberant and breathtaking pag Patience is a psychedelic
                science-fiction love story, veering with uncanny precision from violent destruction to deeply personal
                tenderness in a way that is both quintessentially “Clowesian” and utterly unique in the author’s body of
                work. This 180-page, full-color original graphic novel affords Clowes the opportunity to draw some of
                the most exuberant and breathtaking pages of his life, and to tell his most suspenseful, surprising and
                affecting story yet. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/01/72/01726c619a05114dca75bd840095016d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>685e1b94eecf197afebdd39e91fa4fae</id>
            <title>Are We There Yet?</title>
            <price>10.66</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Caldecott Medalist Dan Santat takes readers on the road trip of a lifetime!"Are we there yet?"
                Every parent has heard this classic kid question on a long car ride--and after reading this
                astonishingly inventive new book (that even turns upside down for several pages!), you'll never look at
                being bored the same way again.Let's face it: everyone knows that car rides can be b Caldecott Medalist
                Dan Santat takes readers on the road trip of a lifetime!"Are we there yet?" Every parent has heard this
                classic kid question on a long car ride--and after reading this astonishingly inventive new book (that
                even turns upside down for several pages!), you'll never look at being bored the same way again.Let's
                face it: everyone knows that car rides can be boring. And when things get boring, time slows down. In
                this book, a boy feels time slowing down so much that it starts going backward--into the time of
                pirates! Of princesses! Of dinosaurs! The boy was just trying to get to his grandmother's birthday
                party, but instead he's traveling through Ancient Egypt and rubbing shoulders with Ben Franklin. When
                time flies, who knows where--or when--he'll end up. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f8/be/f8be3238a1cf039a3e7d50de1d4c2cfd.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f68cbf3f566ad8847c2b00154ca50f43</id>
            <title>When I'm Gone</title>
            <price>51.96</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Dear Luke,First let me say—I love you…I didn’t want to leave you… Luke Richardson has returned
                home after burying Natalie, his beloved wife of sixteen years, ready to face the hard job of raising
                their three children alone. But there’s something he’s not prepared for—a blue envelope with his name
                scrawled across the front in Natalie’s handwriting, waiting for him on the f Dear Luke,First let me
                say—I love you…I didn’t want to leave you… Luke Richardson has returned home after burying Natalie, his
                beloved wife of sixteen years, ready to face the hard job of raising their three children alone. But
                there’s something he’s not prepared for—a blue envelope with his name scrawled across the front in
                Natalie’s handwriting, waiting for him on the floor of their suburban Michigan home.The letter inside,
                written on the first day of Natalie’s cancer treatment a year ago, turns out to be the first of many.
                Luke is convinced they’re genuine, but who is delivering them? As his obsession with the letters grows,
                Luke uncovers long-buried secrets that make him question everything he knew about his wife and their
                family. But the revelations also point the way toward a future where love goes on—in written words, in
                memories, and in the promises it’s never too late to keep. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/13/a3/13a361d57f2b6021b2ae395a6fedd475.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>489db46f1712bc655b8438101118097e</id>
            <title>Luckiest Girl Alive</title>
            <price>49.83</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>HER PERFECT LIFE IS A PERFECT LIE.As a teenager at the prestigious Bradley School, Ani FaNelli
                endured a shocking, public humiliation that left her desperate to reinvent herself. Now, with a
                glamorous job, expensive wardrobe, and handsome blue blood fiancé, she’s this close to living the
                perfect life she’s worked so hard to achieve.But Ani has a secret.There’s something el HER PERFECT LIFE
                IS A PERFECT LIE.As a teenager at the prestigious Bradley School, Ani FaNelli endured a shocking, public
                humiliation that left her desperate to reinvent herself. Now, with a glamorous job, expensive wardrobe,
                and handsome blue blood fiancé, she’s this close to living the perfect life she’s worked so hard to
                achieve.But Ani has a secret.There’s something else buried in her past that still haunts her, something
                private and painful that threatens to bubble to the surface and destroy everything.With a singular voice
                and twists you won’t see coming, Luckiest Girl Alive explores the unbearable pressure that so many women
                feel to “have it all” and introduces a heroine whose sharp edges and cutthroat ambition have been
                protecting a scandalous truth, and a heart that's bigger than it first appears.The question remains:
                will breaking her silence destroy all that she has worked for—or, will it at long last, set Ani free?
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/81/c0/81c0a1ce03db82568e2496db945a8227.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>513f6ea4d971f9b09c2b139a43866b75</id>
            <title>Rising Strong</title>
            <price>21.82</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>The physics of vulnerability is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. The
                author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Daring Greatly and The Gifts of Imperfection tells us what
                it takes to get back up, and how owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us
                the power to write a daring new ending. Struggle, Brené Brown writes, can The physics of vulnerability
                is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. The author of the #1 New York Times
                bestsellers Daring Greatly and The Gifts of Imperfection tells us what it takes to get back up, and how
                owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us the power to write a daring new
                ending. Struggle, Brené Brown writes, can be our greatest call to courage, and rising strong our
                clearest path to deeper meaning, wisdom, and hope. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/3b/f3/3bf3c719382c03984ab9766803bed964.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>3db464906b768db4da4eb89e6c7153a7</id>
            <title>A Hero's Curse (The Unseen Chronicles #1)</title>
            <price>50.49</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>9</availability_count>
            <description>Essie Brightsday has never heard a rock basilisk scream. She has never worn magical armor,
                stood up to a queen, or run from dragons. Instead, Essie, her sarcastic cat Tigrabum, (just call him
                "Tig"), and her secretive family struggle to survive on their small farm nestled against the forbidding
                cliffs of the Valley of Fire. But all that is about to change when a rebellion Essie Brightsday has
                never heard a rock basilisk scream. She has never worn magical armor, stood up to a queen, or run from
                dragons. Instead, Essie, her sarcastic cat Tigrabum, (just call him "Tig"), and her secretive family
                struggle to survive on their small farm nestled against the forbidding cliffs of the Valley of Fire. But
                all that is about to change when a rebellion against the cruel interim ruler is sparked. Forced to flee
                for their lives, Essie and Tig lose themselves in the twisting labyrinth of the ancient lava flow. When
                Essie finds proof that the missing King Mactogonii may be alive, she is given the opportunity to help
                restore stability to the kingdom. But the course of her journey will force her to face her deepest fears
                and unravel the mystery behind her own blindness...if Essie can survive the encounter. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/95/68/95685fabe00befa6dc91277cde703b55.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>c5d98bfb1b49b18c55b8169e86685e73</id>
            <title>Wild: From Lost to Found on the Pacific Crest Trail</title>
            <price>46.02</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER, SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE.At twenty-two, Cheryl Strayed thought
                she had lost everything. In the wake of her mother’s death, her family scattered and her own marriage
                was soon destroyed. Four years later, with nothing more to lose, she made the most impulsive decision of
                her life. With no experience or training, driven only by blind will, she #1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER, SOON TO
                BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE.At twenty-two, Cheryl Strayed thought she had lost everything. In the wake of
                her mother’s death, her family scattered and her own marriage was soon destroyed. Four years later, with
                nothing more to lose, she made the most impulsive decision of her life. With no experience or training,
                driven only by blind will, she would hike more than a thousand miles of the Pacific Crest Trail from the
                Mojave Desert through California and Oregon to Washington State — and she would do it alone.Told with
                suspense and style, sparkling with warmth and humor, Wild powerfully captures the terrors and pleasures
                of one young woman forging ahead against all odds on a journey that maddened, strengthened, and
                ultimately healed her. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/c8/41/c841873951efb18dea28162452efff58.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>015447702942f5906a377d529b249b9d</id>
            <title>Silence in the Dark (Logan Point #4)</title>
            <price>58.33</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>Two years ago, Bailey Adams broke off her engagement to Danny Maxwell and fled Logan Point for
                the mission field in Chihuahua, Mexico. Now she's about to return home to the States, but there's just
                one problem. After Bailey meets with the uncle of one of the mission children in the city, she barely
                escapes a sudden danger. Now she's on the run--she just doesn't know from w Two years ago, Bailey Adams
                broke off her engagement to Danny Maxwell and fled Logan Point for the mission field in Chihuahua,
                Mexico. Now she's about to return home to the States, but there's just one problem. After Bailey meets
                with the uncle of one of the mission children in the city, she barely escapes a sudden danger. Now she's
                on the run--she just doesn't know from whom. To make matters worse, people who help her along the way
                find themselves in danger too--including Danny. Who is after her? Will they ever let up? And in the
                midst of the chaos, can Bailey keep herself from falling in love with her rescuer all over again?With
                lean, fast-paced prose that keeps readers turning the pages, Patricia Bradley pens a superb story of
                suspense and second chances. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>34c17060c25f5164cb42f091b8c5b044</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/bb/1c/bb1c91883579f1f99fe6ebf13b92c1c1.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>58661e0ebc522af16b6de2a3d3ff4396</id>
            <title>The Communist Manifesto</title>
            <price>14.76</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>A rousing call to arms whose influence is still felt today, Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels' The
                Communist Manifesto is edited with an introduction by Gareth Stedman-Jones in Penguin Classics.Marx and
                Engels's revolutionary summons to the working classes, The Communist Manifesto is one of the most
                important political theories ever formulated. After four years of collaborati A rousing call to arms
                whose influence is still felt today, Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels' The Communist Manifesto is edited
                with an introduction by Gareth Stedman-Jones in Penguin Classics.Marx and Engels's revolutionary summons
                to the working classes, The Communist Manifesto is one of the most important political theories ever
                formulated. After four years of collaboration, they produced an incisive account of their idea of
                Communism, in which they envisage a society without classes, private property or a state, arguing that
                the exploitation of industrial workers will eventually lead to a revolution in which Capitalism is
                overthrown. This vision provided the theoretical basis of political systems in Russia, China, Cuba and
                Eastern Europe, affecting the lives of millions. The Communist Manifesto still remains a landmark text:
                a work that continues to influence and provoke debate on capitalism and class.Gareth Stedman Jones's
                extensive and scholarly introduction provides an unique assessment of the place of The Communist
                Manifesto in history, and its continuing relevance as a depiction of global capitalism. This edition
                reproduces Samuel Moore's translation of 1888 and contains a guide to further reading, notes and an
                index.Karl Marx (1818-1883) was born in Trier, Germany and studied law at Bonn and Berlin. He settled in
                London, where he studied economics and wrote the first volume of his major work, Das Kapital (1867, with
                two further volumes in 1884 and 1894). He is buried in Highgate Cemetery, London.Friedrich Engels
                (1820-1895), as well as his collaboration with Marx, was the author of The Condition of the Working
                Class in England (1845), based on personal observations and research.If you enjoyed The Communist
                Manifesto, you might like Marx's Capital, also available in Penguin Classics.'The words of the Communist
                Manifesto flare like the fiery writing on the wall above the crumbling bastions of capitalist society:
                socialism or barbarism!'Rosa Luxemburg ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/bb/cd/bbcd1a94ebc9fb56f8d079df4557f8e2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>907f9b799f8d15980703bf43ee5755ef</id>
            <title>Ouran High School Host Club, Vol. 1 (Ouran High School Host Club #1)</title>
            <price>29.87</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>One day, Haruhi, a scholarship student at exclusive Ouran High School, breaks an $80,000 vase
                that belongs to the 'Host Club', a mysterious campus group consisting of six super-rich (and gorgeous)
                guys. To pay back the damages, she is forced to work for the club, and it's there that she discovers
                just how wealthy the boys are and how different they are from everybody else.
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/d5/c5/d5c5a6ebf05b68bee78a38a8ea62305d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>48cd9c1eb3f173736b09550e834fdb77</id>
            <title>The God Delusion</title>
            <price>46.85</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>6</availability_count>
            <description>A preeminent scientist -- and the world's most prominent atheist -- asserts the irrationality
                of belief in God and the grievous harm religion has inflicted on society, from the Crusades to 9/11.With
                rigor and wit, Dawkins examines God in all his forms, from the sex-obsessed tyrant of the Old Testament
                to the more benign (but still illogical) Celestial Watchmaker favored by A preeminent scientist -- and
                the world's most prominent atheist -- asserts the irrationality of belief in God and the grievous harm
                religion has inflicted on society, from the Crusades to 9/11.With rigor and wit, Dawkins examines God in
                all his forms, from the sex-obsessed tyrant of the Old Testament to the more benign (but still
                illogical) Celestial Watchmaker favored by some Enlightenment thinkers. He eviscerates the major
                arguments for religion and demonstrates the supreme improbability of a supreme being. He shows how
                religion fuels war, foments bigotry, and abuses children, buttressing his points with historical and
                contemporary evidence. The God Delusion makes a compelling case that belief in God is not just wrong but
                potentially deadly. It also offers exhilarating insight into the advantages of atheism to the individual
                and society, not the least of which is a clearer, truer appreciation of the universe's wonders than any
                faith could ever muster. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/36/64/36643d44134c8a227988927013805e61.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f0d487aee0a058c3f436915ea7846550</id>
            <title>Wuthering Heights</title>
            <price>17.73</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Wuthering Heights is a wild, passionate story of the intense and almost demonic love between
                Catherine Earnshaw and Heathcliff, a foundling adopted by Catherine's father. After Mr Earnshaw's death,
                Heathcliff is bullied and humiliated by Catherine's brother Hindley and wrongly believing that his love
                for Catherine is not reciprocated, leaves Wuthering Heights, only to retu Wuthering Heights is a wild,
                passionate story of the intense and almost demonic love between Catherine Earnshaw and Heathcliff, a
                foundling adopted by Catherine's father. After Mr Earnshaw's death, Heathcliff is bullied and humiliated
                by Catherine's brother Hindley and wrongly believing that his love for Catherine is not reciprocated,
                leaves Wuthering Heights, only to return years later as a wealthy and polished man. He proceeds to exact
                a terrible revenge for his former miseries. The action of the story is chaotic and unremittingly
                violent, but the accomplished handling of a complex structure, the evocative descriptions of the lonely
                moorland setting and the poetic grandeur of vision combine to make this unique novel a masterpiece of
                English literature. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>8f67479d76bd33a8c33519a169c2184d</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/93/4e/934e966c1ddf559d3ac2b5c1407aaf1e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>0230adf0e199a0f8be9d444a6d7c38ce</id>
            <title>The Coming Woman: A Novel Based on the Life of the Infamous Feminist, Victoria Woodhull</title>
            <price>17.93</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>19</availability_count>
            <description>"If you have a heart, if you have a soul, Karen Hicks' The Coming Woman will make you fall in
                love with Victoria Woodhull."-Kinky Friedman, author and Governor of the Heart of Texas "What kind of
                confidence would it take for a woman to buck the old boy's club of politics in 1872? More than 140 years
                pre-Hillary, there was Victoria Woodhull. This book takes you back with a "If you have a heart, if you
                have a soul, Karen Hicks' The Coming Woman will make you fall in love with Victoria Woodhull."-Kinky
                Friedman, author and Governor of the Heart of Texas "What kind of confidence would it take for a woman
                to buck the old boy's club of politics in 1872? More than 140 years pre-Hillary, there was Victoria
                Woodhull. This book takes you back with a breathtaking, present-tense bird's eye view into a time when
                women's liberation was primarily confined to one woman's very capable, independent mind. I couldn't put
                it down."---Ruth Buzzi, Golden Globe Award winner and Television Hall of Fame inductee"Sadly, too many
                Americans have never heard of Victoria Woodhull, let alone learned of her story: her revolutionary
                campaign for the presidency at a time when women weren't even allowed to vote, her support for worker's
                rights, or her feminist commitment to equality, a century before the official battle over the Equal
                Rights Amendment. But in The Coming Woman, Karen Hicks brings Woodhull's efforts to life, and reminds us
                that some of our nation's greatest figures aren't always featured in the history books. It is a riveting
                account of an amazing woman and her struggle for justice and human dignity, told in an engaging and
                eminently readable style."-Tim Wise, author, "White Like Me: Reflections on Race from a Privileged
                Son""The Coming Woman" is a novel based on the life of feminist Victoria Woodhull, the first woman to
                run for U.S. President, 50 years before women could even vote!Running for President wasn't Victoria's
                only first as a woman. She was also the first to own a successful Wall Street firm, the first to publish
                a successful national newspaper, and the first to head the two-million-member Spiritualist Association.
                She was the first woman to enter the Senate Judiciary Committee chambers to petition for woman's
                suffrage, her argument changing the entire focus of the suffragist movement by pointing out that the
                14th and 15th Amendments already gave women the vote.In her campaign for the Presidency, Victoria
                Woodhull boldly addressed many of the issues we still face today: equal pay for equal work; freedom in
                love; corporate greed and political corruption fueled by powerful lobbyists; and the increasing
                disparity between the rich and the poor, to name only a few. Her outspoken and common-sense ideas may
                shed a new perspective on the parallel conundrums of today's world.This bold, beautiful, and sexually
                progressive woman dared to take on society and religion. To make an example of the hypocrisy in what
                Mark Twain dubbed The Gilded Age, she exposed the extramarital affairs of the most popular religious
                figure of the day (Henry Ward Beecher). This led to her persecution and imprisonment and the longest,
                most infamous trial of the 19th century. But it did not stop her fight for equality.Victoria's epic
                story, set in the late 1800s, comes to life in a modern, fictional style, while staying true to the
                actual words and views of the many well-known characters. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/3d/54/3d54940e57e662c4dd1f3ff00c78cc64.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4f55d0b77117be942f0da8cfec35b0d5</id>
            <title>Foolproof Preserving: A Guide to Small Batch Jams, Jellies, Pickles, Condiments, and More: A
                Foolproof Guide to Making Small Batch Jams, Jellies, Pickles, Condiments, and More
            </title>
            <price>30.52</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>19</availability_count>
            <description>Canning perfected the America’s Test Kitchen way. The art of preserving produce by canning and
                preserving has come full circle from grandmother's kitchen to a whole new generation now eager to learn
                it. This detailed guide to home preserving is perfect for novice canners and experts alike and offers
                more than 100 foolproof recipes across a wide range of categories, from sw Canning perfected the
                America’s Test Kitchen way. The art of preserving produce by canning and preserving has come full circle
                from grandmother's kitchen to a whole new generation now eager to learn it. This detailed guide to home
                preserving is perfect for novice canners and experts alike and offers more than 100 foolproof recipes
                across a wide range of categories, from sweet jams and jellies to savory jams, vegetables, condiments,
                pickles, whole fruits, and more. Let the experts at America's Test Kitchen show you how to do it right
                with detailed tutorials, troubleshooting tips, equipment information, and insight into the science
                behind canning. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>29e4a3e5b5a3c7fa2cdb4779729a375c</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/9f/59/9f59f01fa916a7bb8f0b28a4012179a4.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>01ef941e27ffe8408c9b2b7b4f8c59b9</id>
            <title>Rogue Lawyer (Rogue Lawyer #1)</title>
            <price>50.11</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>On the right side of the law. Sort of. Sebastian Rudd is not your typical street lawyer. He
                works out of a customized bulletproof van, complete with Wi-Fi, a bar, a small fridge, fine leather
                chairs, a hidden gun compartment, and a heavily armed driver. He has no firm, no partners, no
                associates, and only one employee, his driver, who’s also his bodyguard, law clerk, conf On the right
                side of the law. Sort of.   Sebastian Rudd is not your typical street lawyer. He works out of a
                customized bulletproof van, complete with Wi-Fi, a bar, a small fridge, fine leather chairs, a hidden
                gun compartment, and a heavily armed driver. He has no firm, no partners, no associates, and only one
                employee, his driver, who’s also his bodyguard, law clerk, confidant, and golf caddy. He lives alone in
                a small but extremely safe penthouse apartment, and his primary piece of furniture is a vintage pool
                table. He drinks small-batch bourbon and carries a gun.   Sebastian defends people other lawyers won’t
                go near: a drug-addled, tattooed kid rumored to be in a satanic cult, who is accused of molesting and
                murdering two little girls; a vicious crime lord on death row; a homeowner arrested for shooting at a
                SWAT team that mistakenly invaded his house.  Why these clients? Because he believes everyone is
                entitled to a fair trial, even if he, Sebastian, has to cheat to secure one. He hates injustice, doesn’t
                like insurance companies, banks, or big corporations; he distrusts all levels of government and laughs
                at the justice system’s notions of ethical behavior.   Sebastian Rudd is one of John Grisham’s most
                colorful, outrageous, and vividly drawn characters yet. Gritty, witty, and impossible to put down, Rogue
                Lawyer showcases the master of the legal thriller at his very best. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/92/e4/92e4e180ba8fbde3b8ac0c1e71cfc5f4.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9ee12cde202870f9f1259bf2beb26a66</id>
            <title>The Wedding Pact (The O'Malleys #2)</title>
            <price>32.61</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>New York Times and USA Today bestselling author Katee Robert continues her smoking-hot series
                about the O'Malleys—wealthy, powerful, and full of scandalous family secrets. Carrigan O'Malley has
                always known her arranged marriage would be more about power and prestige than passion. But after one
                taste of the hard-bodied, whiskey-voiced James Halloran, she's ruined for anyo New York Times and USA
                Today bestselling author Katee Robert continues her smoking-hot series about the O'Malleys—wealthy,
                powerful, and full of scandalous family secrets. Carrigan O'Malley has always known her arranged
                marriage would be more about power and prestige than passion. But after one taste of the hard-bodied,
                whiskey-voiced James Halloran, she's ruined for anyone else. Too bad James and his family are enemy
                number 1. Hallorans vs. O'Malleys—that's how it's always been. James should be thinking more about how
                to expand his family's empire instead of how silky Carrigan's skin is against his and how he can next
                get her into his bed. Those are dangerous thoughts. But not nearly as dangerous as he'll be if he can't
                get what he wants: Carrigan by his side for the rest of their lives. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/7e/67/7e67addd80caaf8a9f9e9daa9cf66bb2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>0c1904fe394295528a8c951b39e6ffaa</id>
            <title>America's Cradle of Quarterbacks: Western Pennsylvania's Football Factory from Johnny Unitas to Joe
                Montana
            </title>
            <price>22.5</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>19</availability_count>
            <description>Any fan of the Baltimore Colts of my era, any fan of my friend and teammate Johnny Unitas, or,
                for that matter, any fan of football in general should enjoy Wayne Stewart's book. It contains great
                stories, statistics, and information on all of the many great quarterbacks whocame out of Western
                Pennsylvania and much more. Raymond Berry NFL Hall of Fame Wide Receiver It’s wel Any fan of the
                Baltimore Colts of my era, any fan of my friend and teammate Johnny Unitas, or, for that matter, any fan
                of football in general should enjoy Wayne Stewart's book. It contains great stories, statistics, and
                information on all of the many great quarterbacks whocame out of Western Pennsylvania and much more.
                Raymond Berry NFL Hall of Fame Wide Receiver It’s well known that the NFL has been dominated through the
                years by quarterbacks sown and grown in a relatively small area surrounding the city of Pittsburgh in
                Western Pennsylvania. In America’s Cradle of Quarterbacks, author Wayne Stewart not only tells us who
                they are, he digs deep to explain the nature and nurture behind the rich harvest of signal callers
                (Montana, Unitas, Marino, Namath, Kelly, Blanda, etc.) who have risen from that fertile soil to claim
                Lombardi Trophies and dominate the gallery of busts in the Pro Football Hall of Fame. Stewart has
                written a fascinating book that belongs on the shelves of football historians and everyday fans alike.
                Jeffrey J. Miller Author of Rockin’ The Rockpile, Buffalo’sForgotten Champions, and Game Changers
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ef/0b/ef0bed08de4e083dba5e20fdb98d9c36.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>a0de6ee05916cc08aac1d33e7c2635d9</id>
            <title>Our Band Could Be Your Life: Scenes from the American Indie Underground, 1981-1991</title>
            <price>57.25</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>19</availability_count>
            <description>This is the never-before-told story of the musical revolution that happened right under the
                nose of the Reagan Eighties--when a small but sprawling network of bands, labels, fanzines, radio
                stations, and other subversives reenergized American rock with punk rock's do-it-yourself credo and
                created music that was deeply personal, often brilliant, always challenging, and imme This is the
                never-before-told story of the musical revolution that happened right under the nose of the Reagan
                Eighties--when a small but sprawling network of bands, labels, fanzines, radio stations, and other
                subversives reenergized American rock with punk rock's do-it-yourself credo and created music that was
                deeply personal, often brilliant, always challenging, and immensely influential. This sweeping chronicle
                of music, politics, drugs, fear, loathing, and faith has been recognized as an indie rock classic in its
                own right. Among the bands profiled: Mission of Burma, Butthole Surfers, The Minutemen, Sonic Youth,
                Black Flag, Big Black, Hüsker Dü, Fugazi, Minor Threat, Mudhoney, The Replacements, Beat Happening, and
                Dinosaur Jr. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>a9a8dcfa66cfe6d431ed158c72efd11f</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/54/60/54607fe8945897cdcced0044103b10b6.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>8b647a3d7b5d45972e27fdf9e8627f7a</id>
            <title>The Mistake (Off-Campus #2)</title>
            <price>43.29</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>He’s a player in more ways than one…College junior John Logan can get any girl he wants. For
                this hockey star, life is a parade of parties and hook-ups, but behind his killer grins and easygoing
                charm, he hides growing despair about the dead-end road he’ll be forced to walk after graduation. A sexy
                encounter with freshman Grace Ivers is just the distraction he needs, but w He’s a player in more ways
                than one…College junior John Logan can get any girl he wants. For this hockey star, life is a parade of
                parties and hook-ups, but behind his killer grins and easygoing charm, he hides growing despair about
                the dead-end road he’ll be forced to walk after graduation. A sexy encounter with freshman Grace Ivers
                is just the distraction he needs, but when a thoughtless mistake pushes her away, Logan plans to spend
                his final year proving to her that he’s worth a second chance.Now he’s going to need to up his
                game…After a less than stellar freshman year, Grace is back at Briar University, older, wiser,
                and so over the arrogant hockey player she nearly handed her V-card to. She’s not a charity case, and
                she’s not the quiet butterfly she was when they first hooked up. If Logan expects her to roll over and
                beg like all his other puck bunnies, he can think again. He wants her back? He’ll have to work for it.
                This time around, she’ll be the one in the driver’s seat…and she plans on driving him wild. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>b6fd3641fbebc17c4f90c5e6ce396069</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a5/43/a543b100a8c1861c1bf5374ca6b576fe.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>63781f84c8af4fd1afb52d0c11290abe</id>
            <title>The Art Forger</title>
            <price>40.76</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>On March 18, 1990, thirteen works of art today worth over $500 million were stolen from the
                Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum in Boston. It remains the largest unsolved art heist in history, and
                Claire Roth, a struggling young artist, is about to discover that there’s more to this crime than meets
                the eye.Making a living reproducing famous artworks for a popular online retai On March 18, 1990,
                thirteen works of art today worth over $500 million were stolen from the Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum
                in Boston. It remains the largest unsolved art heist in history, and Claire Roth, a struggling young
                artist, is about to discover that there’s more to this crime than meets the eye.Making a living
                reproducing famous artworks for a popular online retailer and desperate to improve her situation, Claire
                is lured into a Faustian bargain with Aiden Markel, a powerful gallery owner. She agrees to forge a
                painting—a Degas masterpiece stolen from the Gardner Museum—in exchange for a one-woman show in his
                renowned gallery. But when that very same long-missing Degas painting is delivered to Claire’s studio,
                she begins to suspect that it may itself be a forgery.Her desperate search for the truth leads Claire
                into a labyrinth of deceit where secrets hidden since the late nineteenth century may be the only
                evidence that can now save her life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/70/fa/70fa6c0437d9c97dbeada6bd32bf9d2c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>2d2adf5887968a845aa7bca93f046004</id>
            <title>Listen to Me (Fusion #1)</title>
            <price>58.99</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>In New York Times and USA Today bestselling author Kristen Proby’s brand new series, five best
                friends open a hot new restaurant, but one of them gets much more than she bargained for when a sexy
                former rock star walks through the doors—and into her heart.Seduction is quickly becoming the hottest
                new restaurant in Portland, and Addison Wade is proud to claim 1/5 of the cre In New York Times and USA
                Today bestselling author Kristen Proby’s brand new series, five best friends open a hot new restaurant,
                but one of them gets much more than she bargained for when a sexy former rock star walks through the
                doors—and into her heart.Seduction is quickly becoming the hottest new restaurant in Portland, and
                Addison Wade is proud to claim 1/5 of the credit. She’s determined to make it a success and can’t think
                of a better way to bring in new customers than live music. But when former rock star Jake Keller
                swaggers through the doors to apply for the weekend gig, she knows she’s in trouble. Addie instantly
                recognizes him—his posters were plastered all over her bedroom walls in high school—he’s all bad
                boy...exactly her type and exactly what she doesn’t need.Jake Keller walked away from the limelight five
                years ago and yearns to return to what’s always driven him: the music. If he gets to work for a
                smart-mouthed, funny-as-hell bombshell, all the better. But talking Addie into giving him the job is far
                easier than persuading her that he wants more than a romp in her bed. Just when she begins to drop her
                walls, Jake’s past finally catches up with him.Will Addie be torn apart once again or will Jake be able
                to convince her to drown out her doubts and listen to her heart? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/00/dd/00dd43f59d255cbc16e9d9c9ed20a997.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>ba0cc6439889fe1365d2da2463b61f17</id>
            <title>Living Forward: A Proven Plan to Stop Drifting and Get the Life You Want</title>
            <price>12.55</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>Each of us has but one life to live on this earth. What we do with it is our choice. Are we
                drifting through it as spectators, reacting to our circumstances when necessary and wondering just how
                we got to this point anyway? Or are we directing it, maximizing the joy and potential of every day,
                living with a purpose or mission in mind? Too many of us are doing the former--a Each of us has but one
                life to live on this earth. What we do with it is our choice. Are we drifting through it as spectators,
                reacting to our circumstances when necessary and wondering just how we got to this point anyway? Or are
                we directing it, maximizing the joy and potential of every day, living with a purpose or mission in
                mind? Too many of us are doing the former--and our lives are slipping away one day at a time. But what
                if we treated life like the gift that it is? What if we lived each day as though it were part of a
                bigger picture, a "plan"? That's what "New York Times "bestselling author Michael Hyatt and executive
                coach Daniel Harkavy show us how to do: to design a life with the end in mind, determining in advance
                the outcomes we desire and path to get there. In this step-by-step guide, they share proven principles
                that help readers create a simple but effective life plan so that they can get from where they are now
                to where they really want to be--in every area of life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/c9/76/c9767187068d80827d0967225ce3925d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>cb44e0894b3d0c5b19dfb9b4345fbed7</id>
            <title>For the Love: Fighting for Grace in a World of Impossible Standards</title>
            <price>45.13</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>The popular writer, blogger, and television personality reveals with humor and style how Jesus'
                extravagant grace is the key to dealing with life's biggest challenge: people.The majority of our joys,
                struggles, thrills, and heartbreaks relate to people, beginning first with ourselves and then the people
                we came from, married, birthed, live by, live for, go to church with, The popular writer, blogger, and
                television personality reveals with humor and style how Jesus' extravagant grace is the key to dealing
                with life's biggest challenge: people.The majority of our joys, struggles, thrills, and heartbreaks
                relate to people, beginning first with ourselves and then the people we came from, married, birthed,
                live by, live for, go to church with, don't like, don't understand, fear, struggle with, compare
                ourselves to, and judge. People are the best and worst thing about the human life.Jen Hatmaker knows
                this all too well, and so she reveals how to practice kindness, grace, truthfulness, vision, and love to
                ourselves and those around us. By doing this, For the Love leads our generation to reimagine Jesus'
                grace as a way of life, and it does it in a funny yet profound manner that Christian readers will love.
                Along the way, Hatmaker shows readers how to reclaim their prophetic voices and become Good News again
                to a hurting, polarized world. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a7/d8/a7d8fda2a874567aab8f61b2b141a5e2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>a554804438a6695c81af8d57b53cb3ae</id>
            <title>Neither Here nor There: Travels in Europe</title>
            <price>38.95</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Bill Bryson's first travel book, The Lost Continent, was unanimously acclaimed as one of the
                funniest books in years. In Neither Here nor There he brings his unique brand of humour to bear on
                Europe as he shoulders his backpack, keeps a tight hold on his wallet, and journeys from Hammerfest, the
                northernmost town on the continent, to Istanbul on the cusp of Asia. Fluent in Bill Bryson's first
                travel book, The Lost Continent, was unanimously acclaimed as one of the funniest books in years. In
                Neither Here nor There he brings his unique brand of humour to bear on Europe as he shoulders his
                backpack, keeps a tight hold on his wallet, and journeys from Hammerfest, the northernmost town on the
                continent, to Istanbul on the cusp of Asia. Fluent in, oh, at least one language, he retraces his
                travels as a student twenty years before.Whether braving the homicidal motorist of Paris, being robbed
                by gypsies in Florence, attempting not to order tripe and eyeballs in a German restaurant,
                window-shopping in the sex shops of the Reeperbahn or disputing his hotel bill in Copenhagen, Bryson
                takes in the sights, dissects the culture and illuminates each place and person with his hilariously
                caustic observations. He even goes to Liechtenstein. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>1d4d39d152711c55a32fa4724cec47e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/06/81/0681530a7bc301caf5c3257e1b0f0750.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e6d9372ab53aa8b6876127a47d78e4ad</id>
            <title>Little Red</title>
            <price>13.47</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>On her way to Grandmas house, Little Red Riding Hood meets a wolf. Now, that might scare some
                little girlsbut not this little girl! She knows just what the wolf is up to, and shes not going to let
                him get away with it. In this updated fairy tale with a mischievous twist, talented newcomer Bethan
                Woollvin uses sly humor, striking visuals, and a dark irreverence to turn a fa On her way to Grandmas
                house, Little Red Riding Hood meets a wolf. Now, that might scare some little girlsbut not this little
                girl! She knows just what the wolf is up to, and shes not going to let him get away with it. In this
                updated fairy tale with a mischievous twist, talented newcomer Bethan Woollvin uses sly humor, striking
                visuals, and a dark irreverence to turn a familiar tale on its head. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/80/25/8025b80a40178f2a6dd4f99ad88e0fba.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>345fa3f2ead5ccca4d9f02cf69056c9f</id>
            <title>Lord of the Flies</title>
            <price>24.89</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Since it was first published in 1954, William Golding's classic debut novel has remained a
                stark allegory of civilization, survival, and human nature. As dystopian stories like Hunger Games and
                Battle Royale surge in popularity, this haunting tale of a group of young boys stranded on a desert
                island still captivates schoolchildren around the world, raising timeless and pro Since it was first
                published in 1954, William Golding's classic debut novel has remained a stark allegory of civilization,
                survival, and human nature. As dystopian stories like Hunger Games and Battle Royale surge in
                popularity, this haunting tale of a group of young boys stranded on a desert island still captivates
                schoolchildren around the world, raising timeless and profound questions about how easily society can
                slip into chaos and savagery when rules and order have been abandoned.When a plane crashes on a remote
                island, a small group of schoolboys are the sole survivors. From the prophetic Simon and virtuous Ralph
                to the lovable Piggy and brutish Jack, each of the boys attempts to establish control as the reality-
                and brutal savagery-of their situation sets in.A teacher himself, Golding clearly understood how to
                interest children with a gripping story and strong, sympathetic characters. The novel serves as a
                catalyst for thought-provoking discussion and analysis of universal issues, not only concerning the
                capabilities of humans for good and evil and the fragility of moral inhibition, but beyond.The boys'
                struggle to find a way of existing in a community with no fixed boundaries invites readers to evaluate
                the concepts involved in social and political constructs and moral frameworks. Symbolism is strong
                throughout, revealing both the boys' capacity for empathy and hope, as well as illuminating the darkest
                corners of the human spirit. Ideas of community, leadership, and the rule of law are called into
                question as the reader has to consider who has a right to power, why, and what the consequences of the
                acquisition of power may be.Often compared to Catcher in the Rye, Lord of the Flies also represents a
                coming-of-age story of innocence lost. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/33/73/3373a168b588e3fb19c558a21da71ac9.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>6077610fef7a79b09de26f24ae789513</id>
            <title>The Course of Love</title>
            <price>16.78</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>2</availability_count>
            <description>The long-awaited and beguiling second novel from Alain de Botton that tracks the beautifully
                complicated arc of a romantic partnership, from the internationally bestselling author of On Love and
                How Proust Can Change Your Life.We all know the headiness and excitement of the early days of love. But
                what comes after? In Edinburgh, a couple, Rabih and Kirsten, fall in love. T The long-awaited and
                beguiling second novel from Alain de Botton that tracks the beautifully complicated arc of a romantic
                partnership, from the internationally bestselling author of On Love and How Proust Can Change Your
                Life.We all know the headiness and excitement of the early days of love. But what comes after? In
                Edinburgh, a couple, Rabih and Kirsten, fall in love. They get married, they have children—but no
                long-term relationship is as simple as “happily ever after.” The Course of Love is a novel that explores
                what happens after the birth of love, what it takes to maintain love, and what happens to our original
                ideals under the pressures of an average existence. You experience, along with Rabih and Kirsten, the
                first flush of infatuation, the effortlessness of falling into romantic love, and the course of life
                thereafter. Interwoven with their story and its challenges is an overlay of philosophy—an annotation and
                a guide to what we are reading.This is a Romantic novel in the true sense, one interested in exploring
                how love can survive and thrive in the long term. The result is a sensory experience—fictional,
                philosophical, psychological—that urges us to identify deeply with these characters, and to reflect on
                his and her own experiences in love. Fresh, visceral, and utterly compelling, The Course of Love is a
                provocative and life-affirming novel for everyone who believes in love. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f2/c9/f2c952cfbce6ab5d8400a0bb8ee4eb5c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5743b53e7ba0c972ba6b19a14c7d3951</id>
            <title>Angels &amp; Demons (Robert Langdon #1)</title>
            <price>51.48</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>When world-renowned Harvard symbologist Robert Langdon is summoned to a Swiss research facility
                to analyze a mysterious symbol—seared into the chest of a murdered physicist—he discovers evidence of
                the unimaginable: the resurgence of an ancient secret brotherhood known as the Illuminati ... the most
                powerful underground organization ever to walk the earth. The Illuminati h When world-renowned Harvard
                symbologist Robert Langdon is summoned to a Swiss research facility to analyze a mysterious
                symbol—seared into the chest of a murdered physicist—he discovers evidence of the unimaginable: the
                resurgence of an ancient secret brotherhood known as the Illuminati ... the most powerful underground
                organization ever to walk the earth. The Illuminati has now surfaced to carry out the final phase of its
                legendary vendetta against its most hated enemy—the Catholic Church. Langdon’s worst fears are confirmed
                on the eve of the holy conclave, when a messenger of the Illuminati announces they have hidden an
                unstoppable time bomb at the very heart of Vatican City. With the countdown under way, Langdon jets to
                Rome to join forces with Vittoria Vetra, a beautiful and mysterious Italian scientist, to assist the
                Vatican in a desperate bid for survival. Embarking on a frantic hunt through sealed crypts, dangerous
                catacombs, deserted cathedrals, and even the most secretive vault on earth, Langdon and Vetra follow a
                400-year-old trail of ancient symbols that snakes across Rome toward the long-forgotten Illuminati lair
                ... a clandestine location that contains the only hope for Vatican salvation. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/b4/2a/b42a187c37de904f776070c57f51c756.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>f3868e7739e27699dca31e57b47ab3b0</id>
            <title>A Shard of Ice (The Black Symphony Saga #1)</title>
            <price>56.63</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>9</availability_count>
            <description>THEIR SOULS, REAWAKENED.When 13-year-old Lilix Morgan is found alive and floating on a bed of
                ice at sea, everyone counts it a miracle. Kidnapped nearly four weeks earlier, she remembers nothing of
                her mysterious abduction. When she tries to remember what happened, she hears only a melody – a faint
                and delicate set of notes, strung together in a tune she doesn’t understand THEIR SOULS, REAWAKENED.When
                13-year-old Lilix Morgan is found alive and floating on a bed of ice at sea, everyone counts it a
                miracle. Kidnapped nearly four weeks earlier, she remembers nothing of her mysterious abduction. When
                she tries to remember what happened, she hears only a melody – a faint and delicate set of notes, strung
                together in a tune she doesn’t understand. THEIR POWER, UNMATCHED.A year later and desperate to put the
                lingering nightmares of her past behind her, Lilix crosses the country to enroll at Baelmorte Academy,
                aiming to become the violinist she once dreamt of. Things seem to be finally going well, and Lilix
                settles into a routine of sheet music and inspiration among new friends.Then the dreams start. The
                melody and night terrors she thought she’d left behind return with a vengeance, threatening to ruin her
                fragile version of normalcy. Then an unlikely ally tells her that she isn’t alone. That there are others
                just like her, fighting to hide their own shocking truths from coming to light. That they know who she
                is, and what she’s been through. Now, accompanied by four other girls, Lilix discovers her nightmares
                are larger than a single trauma; they’re a window to a hidden part of her soul, a place of immense power
                with a destiny that cannot be ignored. THEIR BATTLE, IS ONLY BEGINNING.With this knowledge comes a new
                and frightening reality. For Lilix has been reawakened to stop an age-old enemy, one thought to have
                been destroyed centuries ago. Trapped by her destiny, Lilix is torn between what feels right and what
                she remembers. Her memories tell her of a star-crossed love waiting to be reunited, of friendships and
                trust broken in the past. But can she save that love when reality brings her an enemy, and an evil that
                will be the undoing of them all if they don’t destroy it? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>db57807585822a8b22d7b172245e20b7</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/27/64/27649cb5da52970f4bb2fc5234a48578.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>303077443f88c476cc70e8fe3acb4223</id>
            <title>Is Everyone Hanging Out Without Me? (And Other Concerns)</title>
            <price>20.11</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Mindy Kaling has lived many lives: the obedient child of immigrant professionals, a timid
                chubster afraid of her own bike, a Ben Affleck–impersonating Off-Broadway performer and playwright, and,
                finally, a comedy writer and actress prone to starting fights with her friends and coworkers with the
                sentence “Can I just say one last thing about this, and then I swear I’ll shut Mindy Kaling has lived
                many lives: the obedient child of immigrant professionals, a timid chubster afraid of her own bike, a
                Ben Affleck–impersonating Off-Broadway performer and playwright, and, finally, a comedy writer and
                actress prone to starting fights with her friends and coworkers with the sentence “Can I just say one
                last thing about this, and then I swear I’ll shut up about it?”  Perhaps you want to know what Mindy
                thinks makes a great best friend (someone who will fill your prescription in the middle of the night),
                or what makes a great guy (one who is aware of all elderly people in any room at any time and acts
                accordingly), or what is the perfect amount of fame (so famous you can never get convicted of murder in
                a court of law), or how to maintain a trim figure (you will not find that information in these pages).
                If so, you’ve come to the right book, mostly! In Is Everyone Hanging Out Without Me?, Mindy invites
                readers on a tour of her life and her unscientific observations on romance, friendship, and Hollywood,
                with several conveniently placed stopping points for you to run errands and make phone calls. Mindy
                Kaling really is just a Girl Next Door—not so much literally anywhere in the continental United States,
                but definitely if you live in India or Sri Lanka. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/6b/94/6b94e98f822a42c03c4ff0b9cfdd6e0c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>e3ec300b05a7104c73796095b2319749</id>
            <title>Original Fake</title>
            <price>31.45</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>In this Banksy-inspired illustrated novel, an escalating sibling rivalry train wrecks and
                vengeance is a street-art act of warIntrovert Frankie Neumann hates his life, and understandably so.
                He’s got a weird, tutu-wearing sister, Lou, and even weirder parents, Bridget and Brett—Frank Sinatra
                and Dr. Frank-N-Furter impersonators, respectively. And, he’s just the guy who mak In this
                Banksy-inspired illustrated novel, an escalating sibling rivalry train wrecks and vengeance is a
                street-art act of warIntrovert Frankie Neumann hates his life, and understandably so. He’s got a weird,
                tutu-wearing sister, Lou, and even weirder parents, Bridget and Brett—Frank Sinatra and Dr.
                Frank-N-Furter impersonators, respectively. And, he’s just the guy who makes pizza at Pizza Vendetta.
                Though he has secret artistic aspirations of his own, his over-the-top family makes him want to stay in
                the background. But Frankie's life is about to change—becoming way more interesting, even a little
                dangerous, but definitely cool.After his shift at the pizzeria one night, Frankie meets David and Rory,
                cousins and errand runners for the mysterious Uncle Epic, a legendary anonymous street artist and
                Frankie’s absolute idol. Little could Frankie dream that his new adventures with Uncle Epic would lead
                to the perfect opportunity to strike back at his insufferable sister for a lifetime of torture. But
                things go haywire quicker than you can say “street art kicks righteous ass,” and the lines are suddenly
                blurred between art and Frankie’s real life. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e7/29/e72934871f9b42a807d976670a446e12.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>108b753f47e07bffc06f586978516b0f</id>
            <title>11/22/63</title>
            <price>48.48</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>Life can turn on a dime—or stumble into the extraordinary, as it does for Jake Epping, a high
                school English teacher in Lisbon Falls, Maine. While grading essays by his GED students, Jake reads a
                gruesome, enthralling piece penned by janitor Harry Dunning: fifty years ago, Harry somehow survived his
                father’s sledgehammer slaughter of his entire family. Jake is blown away.. Life can turn on a dime—or
                stumble into the extraordinary, as it does for Jake Epping, a high school English teacher in Lisbon
                Falls, Maine. While grading essays by his GED students, Jake reads a gruesome, enthralling piece penned
                by janitor Harry Dunning: fifty years ago, Harry somehow survived his father’s sledgehammer slaughter of
                his entire family. Jake is blown away...but an even more bizarre secret comes to light when Jake’s
                friend Al, owner of the local diner, enlists Jake to take over the mission that has become his
                obsession—to prevent the Kennedy assassination. How? By stepping through a portal in the diner’s
                storeroom, and into the era of Ike and Elvis, of big American cars, sock hops, and cigarette smoke...
                Finding himself in warmhearted Jodie, Texas, Jake begins a new life. But all turns in the road lead to a
                troubled loner named Lee Harvey Oswald. The course of history is about to be rewritten...and become
                heart-stoppingly suspenseful. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f6/c5/f6c5d27eacb123238f28a32263694d74.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>0bddf1cc781164cd70f2260cd1ec261c</id>
            <title>Candide</title>
            <price>58.63</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Brought up in the household of a powerful Baron, Candide is an open-minded young man, whose
                tutor, Pangloss, has instilled in him the belief that 'all is for the best'. But when his love for the
                Baron's rosy-cheeked daughter is discovered, Candide is cast out to make his own way in the world. And
                so he and his various companions begin a breathless tour of Europe, South Ame Brought up in the
                household of a powerful Baron, Candide is an open-minded young man, whose tutor, Pangloss, has instilled
                in him the belief that 'all is for the best'. But when his love for the Baron's rosy-cheeked daughter is
                discovered, Candide is cast out to make his own way in the world. And so he and his various companions
                begin a breathless tour of Europe, South America and Asia, as an outrageous series of disasters befall
                them - earthquakes, syphilis, a brush with the Inquisition, murder - sorely testing the young hero's
                optimism. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>8f67479d76bd33a8c33519a169c2184d</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e3/c4/e3c4aba2409bb769a6488805e3fc4709.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>553a4d084035725cf4c1405a1f5fa76b</id>
            <title>Shameless</title>
            <price>58.35</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>***USA TODAY BESTSELLER***Brady…What the hell do I know about raising a baby? Nothing. Not a
                goddamn thing. Yet here I am, the sole guardian of my niece. I’d be lost if it weren’t for Katherine,
                the beautiful girl who seems to have all the answers. Katherine, who’s slowly finding her way into my
                cynical heart. I keep reminding myself that I can’t fall for someone when we d ***USA TODAY
                BESTSELLER***Brady…What the hell do I know about raising a baby? Nothing. Not a goddamn thing. Yet here
                I am, the sole guardian of my niece. I’d be lost if it weren’t for Katherine, the beautiful girl who
                seems to have all the answers. Katherine, who’s slowly finding her way into my cynical heart. I keep
                reminding myself that I can’t fall for someone when we don’t have a future. But telling myself this lie
                and believing it are two different things. Katherine…When Brady shows up on a Harley, looking like an
                avenging angel—six feet, three inches of chiseled muscle, eyes the color of wild sage, and sun-kissed
                skin emblazoned with tattoos—I’m not sure if I should fall at his feet or run like hell. Because if I
                tell him what happened the night his family died, he might hate me. What I don’t count on are the nights
                we spend together trying to forget the heartache that brought us here. I promise him it won’t mean
                anything, that I won’t fall in love. I shouldn’t make promises I can’t keep.* Author's note: Due to
                mature situations and sexual content, Shameless is recommended for readers 18+. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>b6fd3641fbebc17c4f90c5e6ce396069</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a2/19/a2198abf12e3287f84997b35f4e1050e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>a296202878e06514a8fdb7d1cc661c3e</id>
            <title>I am a Hero Omnibus Volume 1</title>
            <price>54.63</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>The zombie apocalypse has never been more surreal! A mentally unhinged manga artist witnesses
                the beginning of a zombie outbreak in Tokyo, and he's certain of only two things: he's destined to be
                the city's hero, and he possesses something very rare in Japan--an actual firearm! Kengo Hanazawa's
                award-winning series comes to Dark Horse, and this realistically-drawn internat The zombie apocalypse
                has never been more surreal! A mentally unhinged manga artist witnesses the beginning of a zombie
                outbreak in Tokyo, and he's certain of only two things: he's destined to be the city's hero, and he
                possesses something very rare in Japan--an actual firearm! Kengo Hanazawa's award-winning series comes
                to Dark Horse, and this realistically-drawn international bestseller takes us from initial small battles
                for survival to a huge, body-horror epidemic that threatens all of humanity! These special omnibus
                volumes will collect two of the original Japanese books into each Dark Horse edition and include all of
                the color pages."Probably the greatest zombie manga ever." --Jason Thompson (Manga: The Complete Guide)
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/16/d4/16d443437126bf6d536a89312c1995a5.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>cf78e0a6c8636398592500d4f0e3dd45</id>
            <title>The Secret Healer</title>
            <price>34.56</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>In the fourteenth century, opportunities for women are limited to the home. But spirited young
                Madlen finds her calling as assistant to the city’s trusted midwife, Clara. Working alongside Clara,
                Madlen develops a surprisingly soothing technique and quickly becomes a talented healer.After Clara’s
                tragic death, Madlen alone rushes to assist the birth of a local nobleman’s c In the fourteenth century,
                opportunities for women are limited to the home. But spirited young Madlen finds her calling as
                assistant to the city’s trusted midwife, Clara. Working alongside Clara, Madlen develops a surprisingly
                soothing technique and quickly becomes a talented healer.After Clara’s tragic death, Madlen alone rushes
                to assist the birth of a local nobleman’s child. But rather than the joy of birth, Madlen walks into an
                accusation of murder and witchcraft because of her extraordinary gifts. Forced to flee her own town, she
                establishes a new identity in the home of her aunt. Yet even though it endangers her life, she cannot
                resist the urge to help the sick patients who seek out her miraculous treatment. When she meets handsome
                Johannes—an investigator hired by the Church to bring her to justice for sacrilegious acts—she becomes
                drawn to the very man who could destroy her.Will Madlen’s gifts bring about her downfall? Or can love
                and reason prevail in a time of fearful superstition? ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>3aae92034c4be904847d47db512438b3</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/69/d2/69d225899cce0a150c605ead01e02f60.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4fcd8d5dc069b8fbae1ca28e2b0105b7</id>
            <title>The Republic</title>
            <price>33.78</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Presented in the form of a dialogue between Socrates and three different interlocutors, this
                classic text is an enquiry into the notion of a perfect community and the ideal individual within it.
                During the conversation, other questions are raised: what is goodness?; what is reality?; and what is
                knowledge? The Republic also addresses the purpose of education and the role o Presented in the form of
                a dialogue between Socrates and three different interlocutors, this classic text is an enquiry into the
                notion of a perfect community and the ideal individual within it. During the conversation, other
                questions are raised: what is goodness?; what is reality?; and what is knowledge? The Republic also
                addresses the purpose of education and the role of both women and men as guardians of the people. With
                remarkable lucidity and deft use of allegory, Plato arrives at a depiction of a state bound by harmony
                and ruled by philosopher kings. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/7b/2c/7b2cb77c4608fce189caebaa842e135d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>b22dbce84b0a79195c50fcc26e9db504</id>
            <title>The Five Love Languages: How to Express Heartfelt Commitment to Your Mate</title>
            <price>31.05</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>18</availability_count>
            <description>Are you and your spouse speaking the same language? While love is a many splendored thing, it
                is sometimes a very confusing thing, too. And as people come in all varieties, shapes, and sizes, so do
                their choices of personal expressions of love. But more often than not, the giver and the receiver
                express love in two different ways. This can lead to misunderstanding, quarrel Are you and your spouse
                speaking the same language? While love is a many splendored thing, it is sometimes a very confusing
                thing, too. And as people come in all varieties, shapes, and sizes, so do their choices of personal
                expressions of love. But more often than not, the giver and the receiver express love in two different
                ways. This can lead to misunderstanding, quarrels, and even divorce.Quality time, words of affirmation,
                gifts, acts of service, and physical touch are the five basic love languages. Dr. Gary Chapman
                identifies these and guides couples towards a better understanding of their unique languages of love.
                Learn to speak and understand your mate's love language, and in no time you will be able to effectively
                love and truly feel loved in return. Skillful communication is within your grasp! ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/38/c5/38c56fba316c07305643a8065269594e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>787c9350fd7dad8eef0d1aecf48c8b76</id>
            <title>Eat, Pray, Love</title>
            <price>51.32</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>In her early thirties, Elizabeth Gilbert had everything a modern American woman was supposed to
                want--husband, country home, successful career--but instead of feeling happy and fulfilled, she felt
                consumed by panic and confusion. This wise and rapturous book is the story of how she left behind all
                these outward marks of success, and of what she found in their place. Follow In her early thirties,
                Elizabeth Gilbert had everything a modern American woman was supposed to want--husband, country home,
                successful career--but instead of feeling happy and fulfilled, she felt consumed by panic and confusion.
                This wise and rapturous book is the story of how she left behind all these outward marks of success, and
                of what she found in their place. Following a divorce and a crushing depression, Gilbert set out to
                examine three different aspects of her nature, set against the backdrop of three different cultures:
                pleasure in Italy, devotion in India, and on the Indonesian island of Bali, a balance between worldly
                enjoyment and divine transcendence. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/21/95/2195c296e82620593a143356aeaa7745.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>279ff852e8614152677f36b6908f4938</id>
            <title>Rat Queens, Vol. 3: Demons (Rat Queens (Collected Editions) #11-15)</title>
            <price>50.4</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>Having survived the end of the world, the Queens follow Hannah back to where it all began: Mage
                University. A long perilous journey awaits the Rat Queens as they attempt to find out what happened to
                Hannah's father while battling their own demons. Collects RAT QUEENS #11-15
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/f3/ef/f3efd43ae0fa85d9b325d5e8783e7af5.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>470e854895d44994a8d292185f1df0cf</id>
            <title>Art Ops Vol. 1</title>
            <price>48.8</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>Reggie Riot is no one’s idea of a cultural savior. The latchkey child of a busy single mother,
                he’s grown up to be a resentful slacker whose idea of high culture is getting stoned and admiring the
                graffiti in the alley where he scores his weed. His mother, however, is not your average working parent.
                She’s the head of a secret organization called Art Ops, whose mission i Reggie Riot is no one’s idea of
                a cultural savior. The latchkey child of a busy single mother, he’s grown up to be a resentful slacker
                whose idea of high culture is getting stoned and admiring the graffiti in the alley where he scores his
                weed.   His mother, however, is not your average working parent. She’s the head of a secret organization
                called Art Ops, whose mission is protecting the artistic treasures of the world—which have a lot more
                life in them than a casual observer might realize.   Reggie has always shunned his mom’s high-culture
                scene, but a devastating encounter with the shadowy forces menacing the world’s masterpieces has left
                him with a permanent expression of the chaotic power of art flowing through his very veins.   So when
                Art Ops itself suddenly vanishes without a trace, leaving its final rescue—La Gioconda, the Mona Lisa
                herself—out in the cold, it’s up to Reggie and his motley crew—including a masked super-powered
                operative who writes sitcom scripts on spec, a girls-just-wanna-have-fun ’80s music-video icon, and a
                suburban clerk from a mall-punk clothing chain—to come to the rescue.   But do they have what it takes
                to stand up to the dark side of human creativity?   From writer Shaun Simon (co-author of The True Lives
                of the Fabulous Killjoys with My Chemical Romance’s Gerard Way) and artists Michael Allred (co-creator
                of iZOMBIE) and Matt Brundage (The Spirit: The New Adventures) comes ART OPS VOL. 1: HOW TO START A
                RIOT, collecting issues #1-5 of the ongoing VERTIGO series and featuring a special sketchbook section
                from Allred and Brundage. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/0b/b4/0bb4c64f1522c033368df5567a349472.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>aec79f57c48c328c4a0ec6ae48eb0091</id>
            <title>Rain Fish</title>
            <price>23.57</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>Get to know the “rain fish” that come to life during rainstorms in this gorgeous exploration of
                nature with vibrant collage artwork from the Caldecott Honor–winning illustrator of Chicka Chicka Boom
                Boom.When blue sky turns gray and it rains all day, sometimes rain fish come out and play. They swim
                among discards and debris. Do you see them, too? Or is it just me?Through l Get to know the “rain fish”
                that come to life during rainstorms in this gorgeous exploration of nature with vibrant collage artwork
                from the Caldecott Honor–winning illustrator of Chicka Chicka Boom Boom.When blue sky turns gray and it
                rains all day, sometimes rain fish come out and play. They swim among discards and debris. Do you see
                them, too? Or is it just me?Through lyrical text and her incomparable mixed-media collage illustrations,
                Lois Ehlert introduces readers to “rain fish”—the varied, colorful, and unique little collections of
                materials that float along on streams of rain water during storms. From a scrap of newspaper with a
                seashell eye and feather smile to a piece of cardboard with an orange peel eye and a leaf for a fin,
                Ehlert’s rain fish come in all shapes and sizes.Complete with an author’s note explaining how Ehlert
                collected the found materials she used to make the book over the course of a year, Rain Fish is a
                spirited celebration of imagination, creativity, and observing the world in your own way—and it invites
                you to discover your own rain fish. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/bb/e2/bbe26db72b8a32117bfe4981b7cc8147.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>efc3765e6e7af89ab2fb5b4d7583a5ad</id>
            <title>The Firm</title>
            <price>45.56</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>5</availability_count>
            <description>When Mitch McDeere signed on with Bendini, Lambert &amp; Locke of Memphis, he thought that he
                and his beautiful wife, Abby, were on their way. The firm leased him a BMW, paid off his school loans,
                arranged a mortgage, and hired the McDeeres a decorator. Mitch should have remembered what his brother
                Ray–doing fifteen years in a Tennessee jail–already knew: You never get not When Mitch McDeere signed on
                with Bendini, Lambert &amp; Locke of Memphis, he thought that he and his beautiful wife, Abby, were on
                their way. The firm leased him a BMW, paid off his school loans, arranged a mortgage, and hired the
                McDeeres a decorator. Mitch should have remembered what his brother Ray–doing fifteen years in a
                Tennessee jail–already knew: You never get nothing for nothing. Now the FBI has the lowdown on Mitch’s
                firm and needs his help. Mitch is caught between a rock and a hard place, with no choice–if he wants to
                live. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/95/84/95847132a78de44b7249a2d0a3fe3ef6.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>2e64126c5d532b4f34102b6429fdfbba</id>
            <title>My Mrs. Brown</title>
            <price>24.48</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>14</availability_count>
            <description>From William Norwich, the well-known fashion writer and editor, an unforgettable novel about a
                woman with a secret who travels to New York City on a determined quest to buy a special dress that
                represents everything she wants to say about that secret…and herself.Sometimes a dress isn’t just a
                dress.Emilia Brown is a woman of a certain age. She has spent a frugal, useful, a From William Norwich,
                the well-known fashion writer and editor, an unforgettable novel about a woman with a secret who travels
                to New York City on a determined quest to buy a special dress that represents everything she wants to
                say about that secret…and herself.Sometimes a dress isn’t just a dress.Emilia Brown is a woman of a
                certain age. She has spent a frugal, useful, and wholly restrained life in Ashville, a small town in
                Rhode Island. Overlooked especially by the industries of fashion and media, Mrs. Brown is one of today’s
                silent generations of women whose quiet no-frills existences would make them seem invisible. She is a
                genteel woman who has known her share of personal sorrows and quietly carried on, who makes a modest
                living cleaning and running errands at the local beauty parlor, who delights in evening chats with her
                much younger neighbor, twenty-three-year-old Alice Danvers.When the grand dame of Ashville passes away,
                Mrs. Brown is called upon to inventory her estate and comes across a dress that changes everything. This
                isn’t a Cinderella confection; it’s a simple yet exquisitely tailored Oscar de la Renta sheath and
                jacket—a suit that Mrs. Brown realizes, with startling clarity, will say everything she has ever wished
                to convey. She must have it. And so Mrs. Brown begins her odyssey to purchase the dress. For not only is
                the owning of the Oscar de la Renta a must, the intimidating trip to purchase it on Madison Avenue is
                essential as well. If the dress is to give Mrs. Brown a voice, then she must prepare by making the
                daunting journey—both to the emerald city and within herself.Timeless, poignant, and appealing, My Mrs.
                Brown is a novel for every mother in the world, every woman who ever wanted the perfect dress, and every
                child who wanted to give it to her. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>51f84adb786c84d26823afbf74900c07</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e0/79/e07906c1e507055da9a2260a74f58273.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>950734bdc9f556e2df87e8aab36ad49a</id>
            <title>The Lean Startup: How Today's Entrepreneurs Use Continuous Innovation to Create Radically Successful
                Businesses
            </title>
            <price>33.92</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Most startups fail. But many of those failures are preventable. The Lean Startup is a new
                approach being adopted across the globe, changing the way companies are built and new products are
                launched. Eric Ries defines a startup asan organization dedicated to creating something new under
                conditions of extreme uncertainty. This is just as true for one person in a garage or a Most startups
                fail. But many of those failures are preventable.  The Lean Startup is a new approach being adopted
                across the globe, changing the way companies are built and new products are launched. Eric Ries defines
                a startup as an organization dedicated to creating something new under conditions of extreme
                uncertainty. This is just as true for one person in a garage or a group of seasoned professionals in a
                Fortune 500 boardroom. What they have in common is a mission to penetrate that fog of uncertainty to
                discover a successful path to a sustainable business. The Lean Startup approach fosters companies that
                are both more capital efficient and that leverage human creativity more effectively.  Inspired by
                lessons from lean manufacturing, it relies on “validated learning,” rapid scientific experimentation, as
                well as a number of counter-intuitive practices that shorten product development cycles, measure actual
                progress without resorting to vanity metrics, and learn what customers really want. It enables a company
                to shift directions with agility, altering plans inch by inch, minute by minute. Rather than wasting
                time creating elaborate business plans, The Lean Startup offers entrepreneurs - in companies of all
                sizes - a way to test their vision continuously, to adapt and adjust before it’s too late. Ries provides
                a scientific approach to creating and managing successful startups in a age when companies need to
                innovate more than ever. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>383351f1704abf38d77ea6ea4bac1fd5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/39/f1/39f167dff90d7f84f5c8dc5e05d4051b.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>64a0e9e0704c068983ec56569f4371c0</id>
            <title>A Mother's Reckoning: Living in the Aftermath of Tragedy</title>
            <price>19.53</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>11</availability_count>
            <description>On April 20, 1999, Eric Harris and Dylan Klebold walked into Columbine High School in
                Littleton, Colorado. Over the course of minutes, they would kill twelve students and a teacher and wound
                twenty-four others before taking their own lives.For the last sixteen years, Sue Klebold, Dylan’s
                mother, has lived with the indescribable grief and shame of that day. How could her ch On April 20,
                1999, Eric Harris and Dylan Klebold walked into Columbine High School in Littleton, Colorado. Over the
                course of minutes, they would kill twelve students and a teacher and wound twenty-four others before
                taking their own lives. For the last sixteen years, Sue Klebold, Dylan’s mother, has lived with the
                indescribable grief and shame of that day. How could her child, the promising young man she had loved
                and raised, be responsible for such horror? And how, as his mother, had she not known something was
                wrong? Were there subtle signs she had missed? What, if anything, could she have done differently? These
                are questions that Klebold has grappled with every day since the Columbine tragedy. In A Mother’s
                Reckoning, she chronicles with unflinching honesty her journey as a mother trying to come to terms with
                the incomprehensible. In the hope that the insights and understanding she has gained may help other
                families recognize when a child is in distress, she tells her story in full, drawing upon her personal
                journals, the videos and writings that Dylan left behind, and on countless interviews with mental health
                experts. Filled with hard-won wisdom and compassion, A Mother’s Reckoning is a powerful and haunting
                book that sheds light on one of the most pressing issues of our time. And with fresh wounds from the
                recent Newtown and Charleston shootings, never has the need for understanding been more urgent. Author
                profits from the book will be donated to research and to charitable foundations focusing on mental
                health issues ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/28/58/285861a80930ffa7521dcb8bd19656e9.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>ad9445ea7964eeef3665e33894fee3e5</id>
            <title>The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy (Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy #1)</title>
            <price>47.8</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Seconds before the Earth is demolished to make way for a galactic freeway, Arthur Dent is
                plucked off the planet by his friend Ford Prefect, a researcher for the revised edition of The
                Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy who, for the last fifteen years, has been posing as an out-of-work
                actor.Together this dynamic pair begin a journey through space aided by quotes from The Hi Seconds
                before the Earth is demolished to make way for a galactic freeway, Arthur Dent is plucked off the planet
                by his friend Ford Prefect, a researcher for the revised edition of The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy
                who, for the last fifteen years, has been posing as an out-of-work actor.Together this dynamic pair
                begin a journey through space aided by quotes from The Hitchhiker's Guide ("A towel is about the most
                massively useful thing an interstellar hitchhiker can have") and a galaxy-full of fellow travelers:
                Zaphod Beeblebrox--the two-headed, three-armed ex-hippie and totally out-to-lunch president of the
                galaxy; Trillian, Zaphod's girlfriend (formally Tricia McMillan), whom Arthur tried to pick up at a
                cocktail party once upon a time zone; Marvin, a paranoid, brilliant, and chronically depressed robot;
                Veet Voojagig, a former graduate student who is obsessed with the disappearance of all the ballpoint
                pens he bought over the years. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/41/74/41747f533b211d324799a03dc64ed175.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>3085532817f8b298f082d3e43a4c77f2</id>
            <title>The Odyssey</title>
            <price>29.64</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Literature's grandest evocation of life's journey, at once an ageless human story and an
                individual test of moral endurance, Homer's ancient Greek epic The Odyssey is translated by Robert
                Fagles with an introduction and notes by Bernard Knox in Penguin Classics.When Robert Fagles'
                translation of The Iliad was published in 1990, critics and scholars alike hailed it as a mas
                Literature's grandest evocation of life's journey, at once an ageless human story and an individual test
                of moral endurance, Homer's ancient Greek epic The Odyssey is translated by Robert Fagles with an
                introduction and notes by Bernard Knox in Penguin Classics.When Robert Fagles' translation of The Iliad
                was published in 1990, critics and scholars alike hailed it as a masterpiece. Here, one of the great
                modern translators presents us with The Odyssey, Homer's best-loved poem, recounting Odysseus'
                wanderings after the Trojan War. With wit and wile, the 'man of twists and turns' meets the challenges
                of the sea-god Poseidon, and monsters ranging from the many-headed Scylla to the cannibalistic Cyclops
                Polyphemus - only to return after twenty years to a home besieged by his wife Penelope's suitors. In the
                myths and legends retold in this immortal poem, Fagles has captured the energy of Homer's original in a
                bold, contemporary idiom.Seven greek cities claim the honour of being the birthplace of Homer (c.
                8th-7th century BC), the poet to whom the composition of the Iliad and Odyssey are attributed. The Iliad
                is the oldest surviving work of Western literature, but the identity - or even the existence - of Homer
                himself is a complete mystery, with no reliable biographical information having survived.If you enjoyed
                The Odyssey, you might like Robert Fagles' translation of The Iliad, also available in Penguin
                Classics.'Wonderfully readable ... Just the right blend of roughness and sophistication'Ted Hughes'A
                memorable achievement ... Mr Fagles has been remarkably successful in finding a style that is of our
                time and yet timeless'Richard Jenkyns, The New York Times Book Review'His translation of The Odyssey is
                his best work yet'Garry Wills, New Yorker ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/0d/e8/0de8211253c4131e0caf9e8528d99443.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5d0f05c52640b6d62c5a299757c7838e</id>
            <title>Naked</title>
            <price>31.69</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Welcome to the hilarious, strange, elegiac, outrageous world of David Sedaris. In Naked,
                Sedaris turns the mania for memoir on its proverbial ear, mining the exceedingly rich terrain of his
                life, his family, and his unique worldview—a sensibility at once take-no-prisoners sharp and deeply
                charitable. A tart-tongued mother does dead-on imitations of her young son's nervous Welcome to the
                hilarious, strange, elegiac, outrageous world of David Sedaris. In Naked, Sedaris turns the mania for
                memoir on its proverbial ear, mining the exceedingly rich terrain of his life, his family, and his
                unique worldview—a sensibility at once take-no-prisoners sharp and deeply charitable. A tart-tongued
                mother does dead-on imitations of her young son's nervous tics, to the great amusement of his teachers;
                a stint of Kerouackian wandering is undertaken (of course!) with a quadriplegic companion; a family
                gathers for a wedding in the face of imminent death. Through it all is Sedaris's unmistakable voice,
                without doubt one of the freshest in American writing. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>e425fa677bdeec8d601df63539f5e217</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e7/12/e71268a559d73826aa64151d47357a12.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4c2c9795cc774d8e408ff6c041d0190a</id>
            <title>Deliciously Ella Every Day: Quick and Easy Recipes for Gluten-Free Snacks, Packed Lunches, and Simple
                Meals
            </title>
            <price>42.16</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>15</availability_count>
            <description>Delicious plant-based, gluten-free recipes and lifestyle tips for packed lunches, snacks, and
                simple meals that are easy and accessible to everyone—from the author of the international bestseller
                Deliciously Ella.It’s easy to be healthy until you get hungry. Making healthy eating sustainable is
                about two things. One: it’s got to be doable in the context of a time starved l Delicious plant-based,
                gluten-free recipes and lifestyle tips for packed lunches, snacks, and simple meals that are easy and
                accessible to everyone—from the author of the international bestseller Deliciously Ella.It’s easy to be
                healthy until you get hungry. Making healthy eating sustainable is about two things. One: it’s got to be
                doable in the context of a time starved life. Two: it’s got to be delicious. Ella Woodward’s newest
                cookbook Deliciously Ella Every Day offers fantastically appealing and quick recipes for breakfasts,
                packed lunches, snacks on the go, and stress-free meals.The book is packed with more than 100 simple yet
                irresistible plant-based, dairy-free, and gluten-free recipes. Be inspired by Ella’s quick weekday
                dinners, amazingly colorful salads, and incredible ideas for meals and snacks on the go. Favorites
                include the insanely delicious roasted cinnamon and maple trail mix, a super-rich chocolate ganache
                cake, a lovely roasted potato, hazelnut and pomegranate salad with a maple dressing. The book includes a
                section of big-batch cooking, recipes that can be made on the weekend so you can pack satisfying lunches
                or prepare quick, easy dinners during the week—a lovely cauliflower pizza or a stunning mushroom
                risotto.Featuring the top ten rules for living the Deliciously Ella way, tips for eating well without
                breaking the bank, and shopping lists to help you get organized, this is the cookbook you’ve been
                waiting for. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>29e4a3e5b5a3c7fa2cdb4779729a375c</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/20/f2/20f28657b49f8cb24ed2ec6448bb6df3.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>c1286aecfdaadd885586c5b69f09ccc1</id>
            <title>Man's Search for Meaning</title>
            <price>29.48</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>8</availability_count>
            <description>Psychiatrist Viktor Frankl's memoir has riveted generations of readers with its descriptions of
                life in Nazi death camps and its lessons for spiritual survival. Between 1942 and 1945, Frankl labored
                in four different camps, including Auschwitz, while his parents, brother, and pregnant wife perished.
                Based on his own experience and the experiences of others he treated later Psychiatrist Viktor Frankl's
                memoir has riveted generations of readers with its descriptions of life in Nazi death camps and its
                lessons for spiritual survival. Between 1942 and 1945, Frankl labored in four different camps, including
                Auschwitz, while his parents, brother, and pregnant wife perished. Based on his own experience and the
                experiences of others he treated later in his practice, Frankl argues that we cannot avoid suffering,
                but we can choose how to cope with it, find meaning in it, and move forward with renewed purpose.
                Frankl's theory--known as logotherapy, from the Greek word logos ("meaning")--holds that our primary
                drive in life is not pleasure, as Freud maintained, but the discovery and pursuit of what we personally
                find meaningful.At the time of Frankl's death in 1997, Man's Search for Meaning had sold more than 10
                million copies in twenty-four languages. A 1991 reader survey for the Library of Congress that asked
                readers to name a "book that made a difference in your life" found Man's Search for Meaning among the
                ten most influential books in America. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>f32425b9800d4105c084852ecf820b33</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ed/ff/edffa2eec8d96b8ddcd53d5c2eff8453.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>444486c433ff272009bbceb01a36df6f</id>
            <title>Gone with the Wind</title>
            <price>32.49</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Margaret Mitchell's epic novel of love and war won the Pulitzer Prize and one of the most
                popular and celebrated movies of all time. Many novels have been written about the Civil War and its
                aftermath. None take us into the burning fields and cities of the American South as Gone With the Wind
                does, creating haunting scenes and thrilling portraits of characters so vivid tha Margaret Mitchell's
                epic novel of love and war won the Pulitzer Prize and one of the most popular and celebrated movies of
                all time. Many novels have been written about the Civil War and its aftermath. None take us into the
                burning fields and cities of the American South as Gone With the Wind does, creating haunting scenes and
                thrilling portraits of characters so vivid that we remember their words and feel their fear and hunger
                for the rest of our lives. In the two main characters, the white-shouldered, irresistible Scarlett and
                the flashy, contemptuous Rhett, Margaret Mitchell not only conveyed a timeless story of survival under
                the harshest of circumstances, she also created two of the most famous lovers in the English-speaking
                world since Romeo and Juliet. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>8f67479d76bd33a8c33519a169c2184d</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/27/82/2782701b5c877cb063065b9fc14c5b13.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>31cd5a39efba48bbb177fb3912bc203a</id>
            <title>Changing the Game (Play by Play #2)</title>
            <price>13.38</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Most people play by the rules. Gavin and Liz aren't most people....Win at any cost. That's
                always been the mantra of sports agent Liz Darnell. When she carries things too far and risks losing her
                number-one client, baseball pro Gavin Riley, Liz realizes that she'll have to work extra innings to win
                him back. It might not be too much of a stretch. She's had a thing for this Most people play by the
                rules. Gavin and Liz aren't most people....Win at any cost. That's always been the mantra of sports
                agent Liz Darnell. When she carries things too far and risks losing her number-one client, baseball pro
                Gavin Riley, Liz realizes that she'll have to work extra innings to win him back. It might not be too
                much of a stretch. She's had a thing for this player's moves since she first laid eyes on him, and by
                the looks of it, he wants her just as bad.Gavin's more than ready—especially when Liz is offering
                herself as part of the bargain. And as much of her as Gavin wants. For added thrills, he decides to
                throw a little curve ball Liz's way to see just how far she's truly willing to go to keep him as a
                client. But when love unexpectedly enters the playing field, neither Liz nor Gavin are ready for the
                biggest game-changer of them all. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/57/47/57472d9c6d483bee9c38c90bfa10b3ee.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>d3b243997fc7246c19d23864f7b6a2a1</id>
            <title>Meternity</title>
            <price>43.58</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>The novel your book club must discuss!Meghann Foye was interviewed on The TODAY Show and The
                View regarding her new book Meternity."A fresh, contemporary take on love and work, marriage and
                motherhood, Meternity is guaranteed to surprise and delight!" â"Emily Giffin, #1 New York Times
                bestselling author of Something Borrowed and First Comes LoveLike everyone in New York me The novel your
                book club must discuss!Meghann Foye was interviewed on The TODAY Show and The View regarding her new
                book Meternity."A fresh, contemporary take on love and work, marriage and motherhood, Meternity is
                guaranteed to surprise and delight!" â€"Emily Giffin, #1 New York Times bestselling author of Something
                Borrowed and First Comes LoveLike everyone in New York media, editor Liz Buckley runs on cupcakes,
                caffeine and cocktails. But at thirty-one, she's plateaued at Paddy Cakes, a glossy baby magazine that
                flogs thousand-dollar strollers to entitled, hypercompetitive spawn-havers.Liz has spent years working a
                gazillion hours a week picking up the slack for coworkers with kids, and she's tired of it. So one day
                when her stress-related nausea is mistaken for morning sickness by her bossesâ€"boom! Liz is promoted to
                the mommy track. She decides to run with it and plans to use her paid time off to figure out her life:
                work, love and otherwise. It'll be her "meternity" leave.By day, Liz rocks a foam-rubber belly under fab
                maternity outfits. By night, she dumps the bump for karaoke nights and boozy dinners out. But how long
                can she keep up her charadeâ€¦and hide it from the guy who might just be The One?As her "due date"
                approaches, Liz is exhaustedâ€"and exhilaratedâ€"by the ruse, the guilt and the feelings brought on by a
                totally fictional belly-tenantâ€¦about happiness, success, family and the nature of love. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>5f3f6372f39c152e3848fd216044b357</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/39/e3/39e33ebef2d7a35dd6899541eba8306d.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>79cac8d8cbeb28bcea60494ba064377a</id>
            <title>The Sandman, Vol. 1: Preludes and Nocturnes (The Sandman (volumes) #1)</title>
            <price>54.12</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>In 1916, Dream is captured and encased in a glass globe in a failed attempt by a fictional
                Edwardian magician (very much in the vein of Aleister Crowley) named Roderick Burgess to bind Death and
                attain immortality. Dream bides his time for decades until Burgess dies. Afterwards, his son Alexander
                becomes Dream's new captor. Finally, in 1988, Alex's guards grow careless and In 1916, Dream is captured
                and encased in a glass globe in a failed attempt by a fictional Edwardian magician (very much in the
                vein of Aleister Crowley) named Roderick Burgess to bind Death and attain immortality. Dream bides his
                time for decades until Burgess dies. Afterwards, his son Alexander becomes Dream's new captor. Finally,
                in 1988, Alex's guards grow careless and the guards watching him fall asleep in his presence, allowing
                Dream to use the sand from their dream to his benefit. When the guards awake and break the seal Dream
                was in, he is then able to escape. Dream punishes Alex by cursing him to experience an unending series
                of nightmares. The rest of the story concerns Dream's quest to recover his totems of power, which were
                dispersed following his capture: a pouch of sand, a helm and a ruby. The pouch is being kept by a former
                girlfriend of John Constantine's. Once that is recovered, Dream travels to hell to regain the helm from
                a demon, where he incurs the wrath of Lucifer (an enmity that will have major repercussions later in the
                series). The ruby is in the possession of John Dee, a.k.a. Doctor Destiny, a supervillain from the
                Justice League of America series. He has warped and corrupted the ruby, rendering Dream unable to use
                it, and with it he nearly tears apart the Dreaming. However, thinking that it will kill Dream, Dee
                shatters the ruby, inadvertently releasing the power that Dream had stored in the ruby and restoring
                Dream to his full power. The collection ends with "The Sound of Her Wings", an epilogue to the first
                story-arc. This issue introduces a character who has become one of the series' most popular and
                prominent personalities: Dream's older sister Death. She is depicted as an attractive, down-to-earth
                young goth girl, very unlike the traditional personification of death, and spends the issue talking
                Dream out of his brief post-quest depression. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/56/ea/56eac75378feb4cab0dcb9d2101cf58b.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>dc15495762778ed4ca37afbfa838324d</id>
            <title>On a Midnight Clear</title>
            <price>14.07</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>It's Christmas Eve and private investigator Adam Fraley has lost his way while traveling a
                remote rural road in the foothills of the Colorado Rockies during a heavy snowstorm. At a loss as to
                where to turn next, he happens upon an isolated cabin in the woods where he stops to seek directions.
                There to greet him is the dwelling's lone inhabitant, an enchanting young girl wh It's Christmas Eve and
                private investigator Adam Fraley has lost his way while traveling a remote rural road in the foothills
                of the Colorado Rockies during a heavy snowstorm. At a loss as to where to turn next, he happens upon an
                isolated cabin in the woods where he stops to seek directions. There to greet him is the dwelling's lone
                inhabitant, an enchanting young girl who invites him out of the storm. Puzzled by the circumstances of a
                child left home along under such conditions, Fraley soon discovers the horrific reason why, a revelation
                that launches him into an intensive search for both a killer and a trove of buried gold. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/a1/14/a114d70e7babf110ba42a389078e9a45.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>830a8522b52ad48921c4e537dc9a966f</id>
            <title>Dracula</title>
            <price>52.62</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>A rich selection of background and source materials is provided in three areas: Contexts
                includes probable inspirations for Dracula in the earlier works of James Malcolm Rymer and Emily Gerard.
                Also included are a discussion of Stoker's working notes for the novel and "Dracula's Guest," the
                original opening chapter to Dracula. Reviews and Reactions reprints five early revi A rich selection of
                background and source materials is provided in three areas: Contexts includes probable inspirations for
                Dracula in the earlier works of James Malcolm Rymer and Emily Gerard. Also included are a discussion of
                Stoker's working notes for the novel and "Dracula's Guest," the original opening chapter to Dracula.
                Reviews and Reactions reprints five early reviews of the novel. "Dramatic and Film Variations" focuses
                on theater and film adaptations of Dracula, two indications of the novel's unwavering appeal. David J.
                Skal, Gregory A. Waller, and Nina Auerbach offer their varied perspectives. Checklists of both dramatic
                and film adaptations are included.Criticism collects seven theoretical interpretations of Dracula by
                Phyllis A. Roth, Carol A. Senf, Franco Moretti, Christopher Craft, Bram Dijsktra, Stephen D. Arata, and
                Talia Schaffer.A Chronology and a Selected Bibliography are included. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ef/d7/efd7c316b4d60a403ba6d111fdeb2d41.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>ef990327dca214e5eb65da6b7bbc4066</id>
            <title>Forever Rockers (The Rocker #12)</title>
            <price>28.8</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>My Happily Ever After was turning into a living nightmare... All I wanted was Harper's
                happiness and I would move the world to give her anything she ever wanted. We've searched for answers,
                talked about our options, and finally-FINALLY-found hope. Yet, just when things seemed to be perfect, it
                all came crashing down around us all. The one person I've always counted on to h My Happily Ever After
                was turning into a living nightmare... All I wanted was Harper's happiness and I would move the world to
                give her anything she ever wanted. We've searched for answers, talked about our options, and
                finally-FINALLY-found hope. Yet, just when things seemed to be perfect, it all came crashing down around
                us all. The one person I've always counted on to hold us together-to hold me together-was lost in her
                own nightmares and I felt like I was losing everything. Everything. I wasn't going to lose the woman I
                loved. I would hold onto her until the last breath left my body. It was my mistakes that were hurting us
                and I would be the one to fix it. I wouldn't let my past ruin my forever with Harper. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>a9a8dcfa66cfe6d431ed158c72efd11f</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/7f/b0/7fb03a053c270000667a50dd8d594843.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>4f953b3d8f0a32a2a1c88a100500861c</id>
            <title>Walk the Edge (Thunder Road #2)</title>
            <price>32.36</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>One moment of recklessness will change their worlds.Smart. Responsible. That's
                seventeen-year-old Breanna's role in her large family, and heaven forbid she put a toe out of line.
                Until one night of shockingly un-Breanna-like behavior puts her into a vicious cyber-bully's line of
                fire—and brings fellow senior Thomas "Razor" Turner into her life. Razor lives for the Reign of One
                moment of recklessness will change their worlds.Smart. Responsible. That's seventeen-year-old Breanna's
                role in her large family, and heaven forbid she put a toe out of line. Until one night of shockingly
                un-Breanna-like behavior puts her into a vicious cyber-bully's line of fire—and brings fellow senior
                Thomas "Razor" Turner into her life. Razor lives for the Reign of Terror motorcycle club, and good girls
                like Breanna just don't belong. But when he learns she's being blackmailed over a compromising picture
                of the two of them—a picture that turns one unexpected and beautiful moment into ugliness—he knows it's
                time to step outside the rules. And so they make a pact: he'll help her track down her blackmailer, and
                in return she'll help him seek answers to the mystery that's haunted him—one that not even his club
                brothers have been willing to discuss. But the more time they spend together, the more their feelings
                grow. And suddenly they're both walking the edge of discovering who they really are, what they want, and
                where they're going from here. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>316b4899867ffb0d5a3cd904a1c75867</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/61/2c/612ce7fa4cbee472392ce8721a4e863e.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9d077954ae9c5b62dec967cf5c879012</id>
            <title>The Bhagavad Gita</title>
            <price>57.49</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>The Bhagavad Gita is an intensely spiritual work that forms the cornerstone of the Hindu faith,
                and is also one of the masterpieces of Sanskrit poetry. It describes how, at the beginning of a mighty
                battle between the Pandava and Kaurava armies, the god Krishna gives spiritual enlightenment to the
                warrior Arjuna, who realizes that the true battle is for his own soul.Juan M The Bhagavad Gita is an
                intensely spiritual work that forms the cornerstone of the Hindu faith, and is also one of the
                masterpieces of Sanskrit poetry. It describes how, at the beginning of a mighty battle between the
                Pandava and Kaurava armies, the god Krishna gives spiritual enlightenment to the warrior Arjuna, who
                realizes that the true battle is for his own soul.Juan Mascaró's translation of The Bhagavad Gita
                captures the extraordinary aural qualities of the original Sanskrit. This edition features a new
                introduction by Simon Brodbeck, which discusses concepts such as dehin, prakriti and karma. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>4135e65298f9865968b7b28f0f69e490</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/4e/69/4e69dacc99de838814d0f65c94e67f6c.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>3e8a2099ecf90803b81cc6819dd17511</id>
            <title>Under the Tuscan Sun</title>
            <price>37.33</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>A CLASSIC FROM THE BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF UNDER MAGNOLIAFrances Mayes—widely published poet,
                gourmet cook, and travel writer—opens the door to a wondrous new world when she buys and restores an
                abandoned villa in the spectacular Tuscan countryside. In evocative language, she brings the reader
                along as she discovers the beauty and simplicity of life in Italy. Mayes also crea A CLASSIC FROM THE
                BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF UNDER MAGNOLIAFrances Mayes—widely published poet, gourmet cook, and travel
                writer—opens the door to a wondrous new world when she buys and restores an abandoned villa in the
                spectacular Tuscan countryside. In evocative language, she brings the reader along as she discovers the
                beauty and simplicity of life in Italy. Mayes also creates dozens of delicious seasonal recipes from her
                traditional kitchen and simple garden, all of which she includes in the book. Doing for Tuscany what
                M.F.K. Fisher and Peter Mayle did for Provence, Mayes writes about the tastes and pleasures of a foreign
                country with gusto and passion. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>1d4d39d152711c55a32fa4724cec47e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/98/c2/98c2e95c5fd1a4e7cd5f2b63c52826cb.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>8b9d676c64d06e201a1d3c2c32fbfb4d</id>
            <title>Mere Christianity</title>
            <price>48.51</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>6</availability_count>
            <description>Mere Christianity is C.S. Lewis's forceful and accessible doctrine of Christian belief. First
                heard as informal radio broadcasts and then published as three separate books - The Case for
                Christianity, Christian Behavior, and Beyond Personality - Mere Christianity brings together what Lewis
                saw as the fundamental truths of the religion. Rejecting the boundaries that divide Mere Christianity is
                C.S. Lewis's forceful and accessible doctrine of Christian belief. First heard as informal radio
                broadcasts and then published as three separate books - The Case for Christianity, Christian Behavior,
                and Beyond Personality - Mere Christianity brings together what Lewis saw as the fundamental truths of
                the religion. Rejecting the boundaries that divide Christianity's many denominations, C.S. Lewis finds a
                common ground on which all those who have Christian faith can stand together, proving that "at the
                centre of each there is something, or a Someone, who against all divergences of belief, all differences
                of temperament, all memories of mutual persecution, speaks the same voice." ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>df5bd314fe6e0e3bd47c8d1dc47290e2</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/d2/90/d29093abd0b9d5258e2e08b731778158.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>9e3a0c61f961bad1d30df453a96637d1</id>
            <title>The Shining (The Shining #1)</title>
            <price>27.88</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>4</availability_count>
            <description>Danny was only five years old but in the words of old Mr Halloran he was a 'shiner', aglow with
                psychic voltage. When his father became caretaker of the Overlook Hotel his visions grew frighteningly
                out of control. As winter closed in and blizzards cut them off, the hotel seemed to develop a life of
                its own. It was meant to be empty, but who was the lady in Room 217, and w Danny was only five years old
                but in the words of old Mr Halloran he was a 'shiner', aglow with psychic voltage. When his father
                became caretaker of the Overlook Hotel his visions grew frighteningly out of control. As winter closed
                in and blizzards cut them off, the hotel seemed to develop a life of its own. It was meant to be empty,
                but who was the lady in Room 217, and who were the masked guests going up and down in the elevator? And
                why did the hedges shaped like animals seem so alive? Somewhere, somehow there was an evil force in the
                hotel - and that too had begun to shine... ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/db/96/db9686744f93c0e9ff3945144827f99a.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>33221179d923a268a6b42be4ad8f0123</id>
            <title>The Exiled</title>
            <price>43.45</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Can anyone ever truly outrun his past?Back in the 1980s, Wes Raney was an ambitious New York
                City Narcotics Detective with a growing drug habit of his own. While working undercover on a high-risk
                case, he made decisions that ultimately cost him not only his career, but also his family. Disgraced,
                Raney fled-but history is finally catching up with him.Now in his early forti Can anyone ever truly
                outrun his past?Back in the 1980s, Wes Raney was an ambitious New York City Narcotics Detective with a
                growing drug habit of his own. While working undercover on a high-risk case, he made decisions that
                ultimately cost him not only his career, but also his family. Disgraced, Raney fled-but history is
                finally catching up with him.Now in his early forties, Raney has been living in exile, the sole homicide
                investigator covering a two-hundred-mile stretch of desert in New Mexico. His solitude is his
                salvation-but it ends when a brutal drug deal gone wrong results in a triple murder. Staged in a locked
                underground bunker, the crime reawakens Raney's haunted and violent past.From the vast, unforgiving
                landscape of the American west to the mean streets of New York, The Exiled is at once a riveting murder
                mystery and a brilliant portrait of a man on the run from himself, an unforgettable thriller that is
                "impossible to put down" (Frank Bill). ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>280a530c4c5e7c6d9f5e2ef32cdf82d6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/2d/1a/2d1aeb1cc8a23064164e230fa232cc04.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5e7a6aa21759a81761568dc9dafa0b24</id>
            <title>Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (Charlie Bucket #1)</title>
            <price>22.85</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Complete with stunning new movie art for the cover, and an eight-page full-color insert of
                stills from director Tim Burton's new adaptation, Dahl's treasured novel appears unabridged in this
                tie-in edition.
            </description>
            <category_id>d33360cdb739050337be5af3488d890b</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/d6/cc/d6cc0c66e34dfc214b406208bbaf18e2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5772b70056f01a96205ad8da270f8e05</id>
            <title>Lumberjanes, Vol. 1: Beware the Kitten Holy (Lumberjanes #1-4)</title>
            <price>45.61</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>16</availability_count>
            <description>FRIENDSHIP TO THE MAX!At Miss Qiunzilla Thiskwin Penniquiqul Thistle Crumpet's camp for
                hard-core lady-types, things are not what they seem. Three-eyed foxes. Secret caves. Anagrams. Luckily,
                Jo, April, Mal, Molly, and Ripley are five rad, butt-kicking best pals determined to have an awesome
                summer together... And they're not gonna let a magical quest or an array of supern FRIENDSHIP TO THE
                MAX!At Miss Qiunzilla Thiskwin Penniquiqul Thistle Crumpet's camp for hard-core lady-types, things are
                not what they seem. Three-eyed foxes. Secret caves. Anagrams. Luckily, Jo, April, Mal, Molly, and Ripley
                are five rad, butt-kicking best pals determined to have an awesome summer together... And they're not
                gonna let a magical quest or an array of supernatural critters get in their way! The mystery keeps
                getting bigger, and it all begins here. Collects Lumberjanes No. 1-4. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/7e/a0/7ea062007ef00107e3c16d336b41fab2.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>78f03d69152775a17cb12f7729ee0b0a</id>
            <title>Ship Leaves Harbor: Essays on Travel by a Recovering Journeyman</title>
            <price>30.6</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>6</availability_count>
            <description>Still scarred from the theft of his belongings in Barcelona, the author returns stateside to
                reassess his dreams for future travel and struggling to regain his love of the journey. From short trips
                along the eastern U.S. seaboard, the author conquers his demons when he takes his family and returns to
                Paris, before heading to a new destination: Lisbon, Portugal.
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/31/b0/31b0e0a42826b326e43235beb8ddd783.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>0c21078de4ab72b63e50a2692ce77698</id>
            <title>The Good Girl</title>
            <price>49.03</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>7</availability_count>
            <description>"I've been following her for the past few days. I know where she buys her groceries, where she
                works. I don't know the color of her eyes or what they look like when she's scared. But I will." One
                night, Mia Dennett enters a bar to meet her on-again, off-again boyfriend. But when he doesn't show, she
                unwisely leaves with an enigmatic stranger. At first Colin Thatcher seems "I've been following her for
                the past few days. I know where she buys her groceries, where she works. I don't know the color of her
                eyes or what they look like when she's scared. But I will." One night, Mia Dennett enters a bar to meet
                her on-again, off-again boyfriend. But when he doesn't show, she unwisely leaves with an enigmatic
                stranger. At first Colin Thatcher seems like a safe one-night stand. But following Colin home will turn
                out to be the worst mistake of Mia's life. When Colin decides to hide Mia in a secluded cabin in rural
                Minnesota instead of delivering her to his employers, Mia's mother, Eve, and detective Gabe Hoffman will
                stop at nothing to find them. But no one could have predicted the emotional entanglements that
                eventually cause this family's world to shatter. An addictively suspenseful and tautly written thriller,
                The Good Girl is a propulsive debut that reveals how even in the perfect family, nothing is as it seems.
                ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>be51785834bf270b101252b8081e7ba6</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/e2/71/e2718be90a081b33d2606a386b073998.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>5fbeef6019688748bdc1e24a4fba2c43</id>
            <title>Prodigy: The Graphic Novel (Legend: The Graphic Novel #2)</title>
            <price>43.63</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>The second book in the best-selling Legend trilogy comes to life in this vibrant graphic novel
                adaptation.After escaping from the Republic's stronghold, Day and June are on the run in Vegas when the
                country learns that their Elector Primo has died and his son has stepped in to take his place. They meet
                up with the rebel stronghold of the Patriots—a large organization strad The second book in the
                best-selling Legend trilogy comes to life in this vibrant graphic novel adaptation.After escaping from
                the Republic's stronghold, Day and June are on the run in Vegas when the country learns that their
                Elector Primo has died and his son has stepped in to take his place. They meet up with the rebel
                stronghold of the Patriots—a large organization straddling the line between the Republic and its warring
                neighbor, the Colonies—and learn about an assassination plot against the Elector. Using threats and
                blackmail to get what he wants, the Patriots' leader, Razor, convinces June to let herself be captured
                by Republic soldiers so she can win over the Elector and feed him a decoy assassination plan. But when
                June realizes that the new Elector is nothing like his father, she must work with Day to try to stop the
                Patriots' plot before Razor can fulfill his own devastating plans. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>10bab9a5f4f4f44e815568924a26a3d5</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/c9/a5/c9a559e3ba407c1d70ebfc4e2f0d82db.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>7c631e4e0373f6a5254fa7853f3af666</id>
            <title>Slow States of Collapse: Poems</title>
            <price>57.31</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>17</availability_count>
            <description>The eagerly anticipated debut from one of Canada’s most exciting new poets In her debut
                collection, Ashley-Elizabeth Best explores the cultivation of resilience during uncertain and often
                trying times. It’s a book built around day-to-day conflicts — poems about love, family, grief, power,
                and longing. Navigating the fault lines of popular culture and traditional poetry to The eagerly
                anticipated debut from one of Canada’s most exciting new poets In her debut collection, Ashley-Elizabeth
                Best explores the cultivation of resilience during uncertain and often trying times. It’s a book built
                around day-to-day conflicts — poems about love, family, grief, power, and longing. Navigating the fault
                lines of popular culture and traditional poetry to assert that we are all history makers, Slow States of
                Collapse enters the landscape of personal narrative in an attempt to reconcile life’s little universal
                griefs.Slow States of Collapse presents a world that is at once menacing and full of wonder and grace.
                It’s a poetry of “casual cruelty” and “kisses like / puncture wounds,” of “something too tender to
                touch” and “the threat of an intense beauty.” In this collection, illness confronts bedside manners
                while a migrant restlessness also paints remarkable portraits of shifting self-image, and in the process
                the nature of personal and political power is reimagined. ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>ba67033c9741930192689a2e7e007b29</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/72/41/72417db983862010ef0c1a25de98c7d7.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>adb5c4fc30ec63d2b8e8eb9031c2812d</id>
            <title>The Rise of Theodore Roosevelt (Theodore Roosevelt #1)</title>
            <price>42.57</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>3</availability_count>
            <description>Selected by the Modern Library as one of the 100 best nonfiction books of all timeDescribed by
                the Chicago Tribune as "a classic," The Rise of Theodore Roosevelt stands as one of the greatest
                biographies of our time. The publication of The Rise of Theodore Roosevelt on September 14th, 2001 marks
                the 100th anniversary of Theodore Roosevelt becoming president.
            </description>
            <category_id>b942462de516c69a778d56ccae99fd15</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/ff/d4/ffd45d95f314555e20c923d3522adea7.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
        <book>
            <id>ea3e72d591755b36fc77ae9f0cb8e583</id>
            <title>Where Lightning Strikes (Bleeding Stars #3)</title>
            <price>39.77</price>
            <rating>3</rating>
            <is_in_stock>true</is_in_stock>
            <availability_count>1</availability_count>
            <description>Do you know what it feels like right before lightning strikes? How you can feel the current
                running through your veins? The trembles of warning that ripple through the air? It was a thrill Tamar
                King chased all her life until it became the very thing she had to escape. For the last four years,
                Tamar King has hidden herself in an isolated world she created. She was safe. No Do you know what it
                feels like right before lightning strikes? How you can feel the current running through your veins? The
                trembles of warning that ripple through the air? It was a thrill Tamar King chased all her life until it
                became the very thing she had to escape. For the last four years, Tamar King has hidden herself in an
                isolated world she created. She was safe. No one could touch her. Until Lyrik West walked through her
                door. He’s the lead guitarist for Sunder and everything she can never have. The dark and beautiful rock
                star becomes everything she craves. Lyrik’s life has been devoted to his band and that success has cost
                him. Bitter, hard, and filled with regret, he refuses to lose himself again, but from the moment he sees
                her, he wants one night with Tamar King. The gorgeous bartender is more than he bargained for. Their
                attraction is consuming. Their desire overpowering. With one touch, they ignite. But is it worth the
                cost of getting burned?She’s a gorgeous nightmare and he’s a wicked dream…WHERE LIGHTNING STRIKES, a
                Bleeding Stars Stand-Alone Novel ...more
            </description>
            <category_id>6e0dad76d05d18a8c397f0d834fdfef1</category_id>
            <book_cover_url>https://books.toscrape.com/media/cache/73/d9/73d948af3f2adb6dd693ff4bd43e7760.jpg
            </book_cover_url>
        </book>
    </books>
</library>